You said your private class
will be done at six o'clock, right?
Yes, what do you think
will be served for dinner?
Are you going straight
to the library?
Don't skip meals because you're
busy. Make sure you come!
Going to eat
will take up so much time.
He's just mad
about his mock exam results.
He can't eat after going from first
to the fifth rank in the province.
See you later!
Hey, Park Jong Hoon! Wait for me!
If you don't come to eat,
I'm going to pack it up for you
and barge into the library!
I'm home!
I'll do it. Go in and rest.
No, you should rest and then study.
Cooking is my study, now.
Don't worry and go ahead in.
Okay!
You said mackerel pike is best
when cooked over a briquette fire.
I also said it's a nostalgic food
for older people.
It's nostalgic for me too.
I don't think I can ever
forget the taste...
of the mackerel pike I had
on my first day here.
That's already
more than ten years ago.
Good work today, everyone.
It's not much,
but I hope you enjoy the meal.
You should show up to school...
as often as you show up
to the diner.
He skipped school today again?
I was on my way to school,
but then something important
came up.
You think you get to skip school
when something comes up?
It's not like I'm going to college.
Why do I need to have
perfect attendance?
Even if you're
not the best student,
I just wanted you
to grow up to be strong.
You really did grow up only strong.
Take your time.
Why are you rushing so much?
Even ten minutes is a waste for me.
Young Shin, I ate as you said.
Don't embarrass me by bringing me
a plate at the library.
Thank you for the meal.
Jung Hoon is the only one...
who seems like a high school senior.
His face looks so
thin from studying.
He said he'll go to medical school
even if he dies trying.
Medical school?
Do you think you can get into med
school just with good grades?
You should study engineering.
You can even get a scholarship.
If I can't get into med school,
I'm going to quit everything
and just get a job.
What? Then how am I supposed
to have fun at college by myself?
Did you even talk to your dad?
I'm probably the only mother...
who gives her senior daughter
a face mask.
When you're done with this,
get to studying.
Aren't you so happy Jung Hoon
is going to medical school?
Are you feeling rushed and trying
to make me all pretty?
Who do you think I am?
Anyway, which college
are you going to?
Is there anywhere you have in mind?
I don't need
to have anywhere in mind.
Based on where Jung Hoon goes,
whichever major it is,
I'm going to go to the same school.
How could you say that?
I'm scared someone might hear you.
I have a cooking certificate,
so I'll work after graduating.
If you're worried about tuition,
don't be.
I have a college savings fund
for you.
When I decided to raise you,
I wanted to make sure you
at least...
could study like other kids.
I'm so happy even like this.
You should've let him send you
to college.
Why are you so confident
with not going?
How much do you think he makes...
selling food for four dollars?
Diner and the house we live in...
are both rentals.
How could I spend
his hard-earned money on tuition?
Then why did you study so hard?
I wanted to beat you. So what?
What?
You know how much
Mr. Jung sacrificed...
for me.
I really want to show him
that I can be happy...
even if I don't go to college.
I mean it!
What brings you here so late?
Well,
Jung Hoon is staying up
all night studying,
and I was wondering...
if you make food for other students.
Oh, that's why you're here?
What would he like?
Oh, right, Mr. Park.
Did you hear that he wants to go
to medical school?
Medical school?
I heard you want
to go to medical school.
You should study engineering.
I can afford that.
I'm not going to study engineering.
I don't want to live like you.
What?
I can't afford medical
school tuition!
Mom said she'll pay.
You're in contact with your mother?
I contacted her first this time.
Did you contacted her...
to ask for tuition money?
Get up!
Get up and look at my face!
Mom is responsible for me too!
What money does your mother have...
to send you to medical school?
She said she has it.
Do you think that's her money?
It's that jerk's money!
He's her husband!
You...
don't know why I divorced
your mother, do you?
I know.
I know, and I knew a long time ago.
You got divorced because she cheated
on you with that man.
I can't believe you know about it
and you still want...
to go to college with his money!
I don't care whose money it is.
I don't even care
if it's stolen money!
I'm going to medical school...
and leaving this tiny town!
- You can't. I won't let you.
- Yes, I can.
Am I your property?
That day that Mom said
she'd take me,
you wanted to take out
your anger on her...
by dragging me
to the middle of nowhere!
Why did you have to drag me here
and ruin my life?
Your father asked me
for a snack in case you got hungry,
so I brought mushroom porridge.
Jung Hoon!
Park Jung Hoon!
We're closed.
Mr. Park!
Do you have any leftovers?
All I need is some kimchi.
Don't worry about anything tonight.
Just have a few drinks
and go to bed.
Although it's a petty life,
I guess I am indeed a foolish man.
I'm not sure if my ego is
hurt or just upset.
But honestly, I can't tell
why I'm in so much pain.
Him saying that I dragged him here
to take out my anger...
on his mother keeps
lingering in my mind.
At the time,
she was crying and begging...
just to take
Jung Hoon and nothing else.
If she said she couldn't take him,
I might have sent him anyway
even if he didn't want to.
Now that I think about it,
I really feel so bad for him...
that it makes me shake.
I only ignored him
because I was sorry.
So,
he can't even look me in the eye.
But actually,
it was me...
who turned away first.
It'll be dawn soon.
You always come here and sit.
Do you want to go somewhere?
When I was young,
I couldn't get on the train and sat
here because I didn't have money...
to buy a train ticket.
Is it because you wanted
to go to your mom?
My mom didn't even care about me,
and my dad neglected me
because of his pains.
I hated them both.
Jung Hoon.
I thought the only way was to study.
Everyone knows
how hard you studied.
I will go to med school.
When I become a doctor,
I will leave this town...
with just one person.
Who is that?
- Is it your dad?
- Are you out of your mind?
Then, is it Da Jung?
Hey! If you leave with her,
what about her parents?
Take her parents with you
if you must leave.
Stop talking nonsense.
I wanted to grab any train
and leave,
but I couldn't leave
because of that person...
and I've been holding on until now.
- Why couldn't you sleep until dawn?
- I was talking with Jung Hoon.
What did you talk about
until dawn in the library?
Don't ask anymore!
I won't tell you anyway.
It's a better world now.
Young Shin and Jung Hoon talk
about secrets without me knowing.
Hey. This is bringing back memories.
What's that look for?
Are you worried about something?
I don't have any secrets from you.
We have no secrets between us.
Jung Hoon gave me
a pretty notebook yesterday.
But he told me not to tell you.
Why is he like that?
I feel really burdened.
Maybe it's because he wants
to get along with you.
Oh Bok!
You're popular
because you're pretty and kind.
I'm too popular. Seriously.
Let's go.
What are you doing here
and not going home?
I was waiting to go with you.
I'm going to go with Young Shin.
Young Shin. I have something
to say to Da Jung.
Can you go first?
Well, okay.
You two talk. I'll go first.
Hey. What do you
and I have so much to talk about?
Hear what he has to say.
See you later at the Diner!
My dad gave me an allowance.
- Let's get tteokbokki!
- Gosh.
How come you're so stingy?
It would be nice
if Young Shin eats with us.
It's because I want to eat with you.
You eat as much as you want!
Young Shin! Wait for me!
Da Jung.
Jun Young, is college fun?
Uncle Jong Gwon! Please buy me
a studio in front of the school!
Not a chance.
What are you trying to do
while you live out?
As he's a boy, it's not bad for him
to live independently early.
It's not good to keep your children
in your arms.
At least give him a chance
to learn how to live in the world.
How can you say that
in this day and age?
I'd probably blow his brains out...
while trying to teach him
about the world.
Well,
what would I know when I haven't
even raised children before?
I almost forgot.
Let's meet tonight, everyone.
I have something to discuss.
I have other companies...
so I'm thinking of removing
my name from the Royal Palace.
What do you guys think?
Do you mean you're withdrawing
from the CEO position?
Do you want to try?
Me?
How can I?
Or Jong Woo, you try it.
Jong Gwon.
It's time for both of you
to become bosses.
You should do this.
I can't do it
as I can't concentrate.
Finally, the moment has come.
If she becomes the CEO,
we will gain nothing.
If we get pushed back here,
we're done.
Do as I say.
Jun Young will take over
the restaurant later.
Wouldn't it be better for me
to teach Jun Young the work...
and manage the restaurant?
- I'm not sure.
- From Sook Jung's point of view,
it'll be awkward for her...
to train Jun Young harshly
as he's not even her child.
It sure is.
Let's think about it.
You're so gentle.
It'll be difficult to have the staff
under your control.
What if you get offended?
In terms of being gentle,
there is no one...
more gentle than Jong Woo and you.
You only cooked
so you're ignorant of the world.
Well, Sook Jung really doesn't
know anything but cooking.
She's so gentle and innocent.
Then let's do this.
As we have to think
about Jun Young too,
you be in charge,
and then hand it over to Jun Young.
Thank you, Jong Gwon!
It's better to do that, right?
Take your time and decide.
What more time does he need?
Jun Young is the only descendant
of this family.
I'm saying this...
as we can't ruin the restaurant
before handing it over to him.
You don't want to hand over
the restaurant in shreds.
Why would the restaurant be
in shreds?
What the heck does she mean that...
the restaurant is going to foreclose
as we have tax delinquencies?
We have some tax delinquencies.
Where is the money to pay this tax?
I did something.
"Did something"?
You're out of your mind, honey!
Don't worry. I'll get the money...
- and pay it back.
- Where from?
How can you get a hold
of such a large amount of money?
If so, you should have told me!
That way, I would've found a way!
I was scared.
See? Even now,
you never let up on me.
What? You were scared?
Am I scary?
Sook Jung is the scary one.
I'm scared of you more.
Goodness. It's unbelievable!
And at a crucial moment!
My blood pressure is going up.
Are you going to the private class?
Did you ask Young Shin
what the side dishes are for dinner?
Oh Bok.
You don't even come to school.
What are you doing there?
Mind your own business.
Do you really want
to live like that?
Are you worried about me?
I'm looking down on you.
How dare you say that?
If you meet me in town from now on,
just ignore me, all right?
- This is a warning.
- Why?
Are you embarrassed
because I pretend to know you?
Didn't you know?
Darn it!
Young Shin!
- This is serious!
- What's wrong?
Oh Bok got into a fight
with gangsters at the crossroads.
What?
- Go quickly and get Yong Goo!
- Right.
Shall we call the police?
Then what if Oh Bok
gets expelled from school?
- He's still a student!
- That's right!
Hey!
All of you, stop it right now!
I called the police!
Do you all want to get arrested?
Stop it at once!
Stop hitting him, you punk!
Hey, Oh Bok.
What is this brat?
This brat is Kim Young Shin.
Haven't you heard
of Kim Young Shin of Diner?
We have the chief of police...
and pastor as our regulars!
So go ahead and hit me!
Once you hit me,
you won't be able to
live normally in this town!
Come on, hit me!
Stop it right now, you punks!
Young Shin.
- Oh Bok.
- Why this little...
Oh Bok!
No, Oh Bok.
Police officer!
Sir, here!
Goodness, my babies!
- What has happened?
- Are you hurt, Young Shin?
- My dear!
- Do you recognize me, Oh Bok?
My goodness, Oh Bok.
So this is how it ends up.
Look at me, Oh Bok.
Are you okay?
Young Shin! Wake up!
My gosh, Young Shin!
Open your eyes!
We need to call 911!
Wake up, Oh Bok.
Come on, carry him already.
Goodness.
Stay with me, Oh Bok.
Oh Bok, for goodness' sake.
Which way is the hospital?
Is it this way? Or that way?
It's this way!
There's nothing to be confused.
You just have to follow them!
You idiot.
Hurry up! Oh Bok, my poor baby.
Young Shin, please wake up.
Oh, dear.
Young Shin.
Are you okay, Young Shin?
I was just startled a bit.
Why would you meddle in boys' fight?
Mr. Jung is furious for real.
What if one of them hit you?
You could've been
seriously dangerous.
I was too frantic
to think reasonably.
You won't be able to see me...
if you meddle in Oh Bok's fight.
Is that supposed to be a threat?
How can you be such smug
even in this situation?
I did warn you.
I bet he's throwing a tantrum
for wasting his time to study.
He acts so well
as if he really cares about you.
He has no serious injury.
He can go home after being treated.
Thank you, doctor.
My goodness.
Gosh, an old lady like me can't
bear this extreme.
Even if I have to search
the whole country,
I'm going to find your parents
and ask them to take you.
But you don't know where they are.
You can't search the whole country.
It's already been ten years
since they left him with me...
saying that they would be back
after they make a raise.
They won't recognize him
in the streets...
even if they run into him.
You should've just let me die.
Why did you carry me
to the hospital?
Why do you belittle yourself?
I don't have the looks,
brain, nor money.
I don't even have parents!
I'm nothing but a moron...
who is too coward
to take his own life.
You should've let them
beat me up to death.
Why did you carry me
to the hospital to save me?
Oh Bok.
Oh Bok!
Come on.
Listen carefully, you.
I won't forgive you
if this happens again.
I couldn't just watch
and let him be beaten to death.
I had meals with him
at the same table for ten years.
If something happens to you,
I won't be able to live a life.
Mr. Jung.
What are you doing there?
You should've come in
if you were hungry.
You've made trouble for me.
What trouble?
Must I be worried about you
at this important period of my life?
It's about time you start
to think of others.
Have some ramyeon while you're here.
Young Shin.
Yes?
Who says I'm here for ramyeon?
Why would you yell at me?
If it's such a waste of your time,
go and study.
I couldn't read a single word...
because of you.
That's why I ended up here.
What?
Why can't you read because of me?
You could just let me
be the bad guy here.
Why would I let you be the bad guy?
Do you really not understand
what I'm saying?
What do you mean?
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
(A Good Supper)
You take responsibility for it.
I will so don't worry.
Men won't tell women anything
that'd make them look pathetic.
Seniors don't have time for that.
It seems you share quite a lot
with Young Shin.
Be nice to Oh Bok.
But he's a nasty piece of work.
We have someone
who needs his nose fixed.
- Get out!
- Uncle!
Fine, you win.
I have to do more
than enough to get them.
I've prepared something.
Now, look. You piece of craps.
I am Choi Sook Jung, the owner
of this great "Royal Palace".