(Episode 91)
The address says it's here.
People don't seem to live
around here.
Why did they ask me to come here?
Move.
Who's up there?
Are you okay?
We should get out of here.
Come on, ma'am.
Are you hurt?
No, I think I'm okay.
Oh, boy.
You must have sprained your ankle.
I'll call an ambulance.
Hello?
Yes, we're at...
Mom!
Su Hee, are you all right?
I told you it's not a big deal.
You didn't have to come here.
What happened? How did you get hurt?
I just sprained my ankle.
You should have been careful.
Where did you get hurt?
But still,
it's fortunate
that it's not serious.
Don't worry, Sang Tae.
I'll be fine after a day or two.
How much...
does Ji Sook remember?
It seems she only remembers
Chairman Cha...
after hearing
that she's Seo Ji Sook.
If she remembers everything,
she wouldn't be staying still
like now.
If she remembers him,
it's only a matter of time
before she remembers me.
So...
we have to keep her away
from my husband.
Find a way!
Yes, ma'am.
Mom,
are you sure you'll be okay
by yourself?
Oh, I said I'm fine.
You said you even had to
bring work home.
You also have to go to work
early tomorrow.
Go on and head home.
But I'm worried.
Oh, gosh. I'm really fine.
Yes, we should go
so that she can get some rest.
If you get sick at night,
call me right away.
I will.
Go ahead.
Min Hyuk,
have a word...
with me before you go.
You got your memory back?
Do you remember everything then?
Not everything.
Why are you with Chairman Cha
in these photos?
I was Seo Ji Sook,
and I had been...
dating Woo Seok.
That's what I remembered.
Then...
does Chairman Cha know
your memory returned as well?
Yes. I talked to him in person.
And as we were parting,
I got a text message.
A text message?
The person said
he or she will tell me...
the truth of the day
I lost my memory.
So I went to
where they told me to be,
but suddenly...
the construction material fell
on my head.
Did you...
see who was there?
No.
Please show me the text.
(If you want to know the truth
about that day, come here.)
Wait, this number is...
These are the call records
between Park Sang Chul...
and Choi Chang Beom in 2015.
The number that's shown
on both their records is...
the culprit's burner phone.
Why? Do you recognize this number?
No.
I'll look into it.
And Su Hee,
when you get this kind of text
from now on,
remember to tell me.
Don't just go there alone.
Okay?
Okay.
Mother, are you just coming home?
Where have you been?
I had some business to take care of
because of the foundation.
I see. Right.
Father's already home.
Is he?
Something good must have
happened to him.
He looked happy.
Do you remember...
why the floral language
of a viola is...
"eternal love"?
You and I...
decided to call it that way.
Ji Sook.
You came home early today.
Yes. Hello.
Did anything good happen?
You look happy.
No,
nothing happened.
So...
Su Hee got her memory back, right?
Yes.
But not in its entirety.
Also,
I think that's what injured her
today.
What do you mean by that?
She received a text...
telling her to come
to the construction site...
if she wants to know the truth.
And...
that's where she was attacked.
Who on earth sent that text?
It was the same burner phone
from five years ago.
It was currently turned off,
so I went to the construction site.
But there aren't any cameras...
nor any unusual traces.
She could have been
seriously injured.
It's lucky her injury isn't
that bad.
Does that mean...
Chairman Cha isn't the one...
who killed my brother
in the hit-and-run?
We can't jump to conclusions yet.
Why?
Chairman Cha and we are
the only ones...
who know that Su Hee got
her memory back.
But...
the day her memory returned,
she was attacked instantly.
Then...
what should we do now?
First, we can't let anyone else
find out...
that her memory has returned.
I'll investigate if someone else...
other than Chairman Cha or us
knows about it.
And...
about Ju Hwa Yeon and Chairman Cha,
we should dig deeper.
If I hadn't retired,
this would have been much easier.
Sang Tae,
I'll clear you of your false charge.
I've been looking for the owner...
of the bar anyway.
You too?
I looked for the owner too,
but it wasn't easy.
I learned that the owner took
a flight to the Philippines,
but after that,
I couldn't find anything else.
I'm still looking,
so please wait.
Thank you for the cellphone.
You're welcome.
I'll go to work first.
Okay.
How long does it take to restore
a cellphone that's been reset?
I'll send it to you right now,
so please get it done
as soon as possible.
If this is restored,
I can put a stop to Yu Ra
who is running amok.
This is Ms. Han Yu Jung's
application form you requested.
Thank you.
(Father: Han Dae Chul,
Mother: Yeo Sook Ja)
It was Dae Chul.
There you were, Ms. Han.
Hello, Mr. Koo.
Were you looking for me?
Now that I look at you,
you really resemble him.
Excuse me?
Your father is Mr. Han Dae Chul,
isn't it?
Do you know my father?
Of course, I do!
I am a very close hometown friend
of his.
I see.
How did you know it was me?
A few days ago, I saw you two
together.
I couldn't get a close look
at the face.
Just in case, I checked your
application form. I was right!
I see.
Dad will be happy if he hears
about you.
It's such a small world.
By the way, you look very healthy.
Your father was having a hard time
because you had to receive...
heart surgery
not long after you were born.
Now that I see you have grown
so healthily,
I am so glad.
Heart surgery?
I've never received it.
Sorry?
You haven't?
You must have been mistaken.
I heard I grew up as a very healthy
child without having any illnesses.
I have to go to a meeting.
I should go first.
Okay.
I will tell Dad you said hello.
Okay. Thank you.
What was that?
He told me
she's getting heart surgery.
Ji Sook, are you okay?
I told you that there is no need
to visit me.
I will soon go home.
How can I not visit?
I was worried about you.
How did you get hurt?
I just sprained my ankle.
Is that so?
I'm relieved that you were not
hurt badly.
I was so worried on the way,
just in case you were hurt severely.
Mom, I heard her memory returned.
I heard from Mr. Koo.
Don't worry.
Her memory hasn't returned entirely.
By the way, I heard she is
hospitalized.
By any chance, this isn't related
to you, is it?
No, I don't know anything about it.
How did you know about that?
I was planning to meet her
for canceling the store contract.
But I couldn't because I was told
she is in the hospital.
You didn't do anything to her,
right?
I told you I didn't!
Woo Seok, you remembered.
Whenever I was sick,
you bought this for me.
You told me this was
the most delicious food.
Do you not like this anymore?
How would I not like this?
You gave this to me.
Then have a bite.
Shall I?
Do you like it?
I do.
It is sweet and delicious.
Is there anything else
you can remember?
I can vaguely...
remember that I was being chased
by someone, but nothing else.
Ms. Kang Ye Jin looked a lot
like you.
Her smile,
her kindness to others as well.
She was like watching
a younger version of you.
Of course, she is my daughter.
Ye Jin resembles me,
which is why she is so pretty.
By the way,
is Ye Jin the only child you have?
Mom, I'm here.
What brings you here, Chairman Cha?
I should be going.
Wait.
Ms. Han.
Why did you have to call Yu Jung
who's innocent and be harsh to her?
Why do you have to make me
so miserable?
Chairman Cha, is there something
you want to tell me?
I apologize for speaking harshly
to you before.
I should have apologized earlier.
I'm sorry.
It is okay. Don't be.
I understand what made you talk
to me that way.
I am sorry too.
Okay, then. You may go now.
Mom, why did Chairman Cha come?
Ye Jin.
Some of my memory has returned.
Really? Which part?
Not all of it.
I could remember my name.
But still, I'm glad.
It's such good news.
Chairman Cha and I...
knew each other in the past.
When I was young,
I grew up in an orphanage.
DL Group sponsored my orphanage.
That is how I got to know him.
I see.
That is amazing.
Hello, Prosecutor Jang?
Did you find that person?
Which penitentiary is he in?
Are you nervous?
I am not nervous.
I am gnashing my teeth!
If I think of my wrongful layoff
from the police because of him,
I can't let go of my anger
even in my sleep!
By the way, how was he caught?
He was imprisoned in the Philippines
for illegal prostitution...
and was transferred recently.
I see.
I won't let him off easy today.
You!
You are so dead!
Why are you doing this to me?
Let go of me. Let go!
Do you know how miserable
I've been because of you?
Did you know you could live well
after framing an innocent person?
You shouldn't be doing this.
Sang Tae, let him go!
Let's talk! Let's use words. Okay?
Sit down.
Long time no see.
Such manners you have to say hello.
You!
Why did you do that to me
five years ago?
You told me those were toilet paper!
Nobody gives bribe money as it is!
You know how it works.
What did you say?
You must be daring to die today,
aren't you?
Why don't we both die in here?
Sang Tae, stop!
Calm down, please!
You ripped my clothes!
Mr. Park Jin Soo.
Let's not waste time.
What's the reason you gave Sang Tae
the bribe he didn't even ask for?
I don't understand a single word
of what you are talking about.
Mr. Park.
You were imprisoned in the
Philippines because of prostitution.
I did some more research...
and it seems like you luckily
got away with drug distribution...
by getting in touch
with Chinese drug dealers.
But what do you think...
will happen if the Chinese police
find out about this?
They wouldn't just sit there,
would they?
You're also aware of that,
so you bought people's silence
in the Philippines.
So what?
What do you want?
"What do you want"?
Tell us the truth.
What is the reason
you framed Sang Tae?
Darn it!
I was paid!
I got a phone call, so I did
what I was ordered to do!
That's really all!
We were right.
Park Jin Soo's call history has...
the same burner phone number.
It's clear that all this is related
to my mom's case.
And now that we have
Park Jin Soo's statement,
you'll be able to clear your name...
if you tell the Audit
and Inspection Division.
Min Hyuk,
thank you so much
for doing all this.
It's nothing.
You were dismissed unfairly.
It's natural for you to have
your name cleared and reinstated.
Okay. Once I'm reinstated,
I'll do my best to help you.
Now that I'm cleared,
I'll also help clear your mother
of her false accusation of murder.
Let's get the real culprit.
Yes, Sang Tae.
Cha Mi Ri.
Why are you back here?
Nothing would change
from coming here.
Forget it.
I'll just leave.
But since I'm here,
should I get a quick look
at Sang Tae?
Mi Ri!
What are you doing here?
Sang Tae...
Mi Ri, are you drunk?
Yes.
I'm completely drunk on you.
That's why I can't sober up.
You can't even drink. Why did you...
drink so much?
Are you worrying about me?
Why did you tell me to break up
if you were going to be so worried?
I can't live without you.
Sang Tae, can't we just get
back together?
I told you we can't.
It might be hard for now,
but time will resolve it.
When?
How long do I have to wait
for it to be resolved?
Here.
Take this.
What is this?
Coffee?
It's your favorite coffee.
Take that...
and enjoy the drink.
You will feel much better...
when you're finished
with that coffee.
All the data deleted on the phone
has been recovered with forensics.
(Birth Certificate)
Yu Ra gave birth?
(Father: Lee Tae Poong,
Mother: Han Yu Ra)
Lee Tae Poong?
Seo Jun, I have to find Tae Poong.
Because of me, Tae Poong is...
Tae Poong!
Yu Jung looked for this man
five years ago in Chuncheon.
Does Yu Jung know
who Lee Tae Poong is?
What is it?
Do you know Lee Tae Poong?
What?
You looked for Lee Tae Poong
five years ago in Chuncheon.
Did you find him back then?
Why do you ask that suddenly?
Yu Ra married Lee Tae Poong
and even had a child.
Did you know about it?
What?
No.
I think I need to meet Mr. Lee.
Where is he now?
Seo Jun doesn't seem to know
that Tae Poong is Min Hyuk yet.
Yu Jung.
I don't know. I couldn't find him.
I see.
But how do you know Mr. Lee?
I just know him.
And I'm not sure if he's
the same person you're looking for.
He might just have the same name.
I see.
You can go now.
Okay.
Yu Ra, see me for a moment.
Seo Jun is looking
for Lee Tae Poong.
He even found out
that Yu Ra gave birth,
and asked me if I knew
where Lee Tae Poong was.
Is that so?
I did tell him I didn't know,
but what if he finds out
about your identity soon?
Don't worry.
Even if Seo Jun tries
to dig into me,
he won't be able to find me.
I deleted every trace of me
left in Chuncheon.
Even the wedding photo
in the photo studio.
I see.
But why do I feel so anxious?
Don't worry. It'll be all right.
But how do you think
Seo Jun found out?
I'm not sure.
Dae Chul,
you haven't changed at all.
Has it been 30 years
since we last met?
Yes.
So, Chun Soo. How have you been?
We were so close by
yet we didn't know.
I found out only recently
that Ms. Han is your daughter.
I'd have found you faster
if only I realized it sooner.
That's right.
By the way, Dae Chul, Ms. Han grew
up to be such a fine lady.
Is she all healthy now?
And is her heart okay?
What?
Back then, you struggled so much
because of her heart issues.
Yes, that's true.
Has her heart been fine
ever since then?
Yes, Seo Jun. I just got here.
I'll wait for you inside.
Come safely.
Her operation went very well.
She's all healthy now.
What is this?
Why is Dad meeting up with Mr. Koo?
I'm glad she's healthy.
By the way, Dae Chul,
that child...
Hey, Chun Soo. I have to go now.
I forgot about an urgent delivery
to make.
Okay, sure.
Hey, Chun Soo, I'm so sorry.
It's not a problem.
I'm so happy to see you.
Let's go for a drink someday.
- Sure.
- I'll get going.
- Go on.
- Bye.
What was that?
Why did you meet up with Mr. Koo?
It's none of your business.
None of my business? What did you
talk about? Tell me now.
Mind your own business.
Dad!
"Dad"?
I'm sorry, Yu Ra.
I don't think I can make it
due to an urgent meeting.
I'll see you at home.
I understand. Okay.
Bye.
That man is Yu Ra's father?
Her father isn't a dentist.
As far as I know, he worked...
as a chauffeur for the owner
of a food company in Chuncheon.
And her mother worked
as a maid for the owner.
I have a request to make.
Could you look
into a food company in Chuncheon?
Yes. The man who worked
as the chauffeur.
And please look into Lee Tae Poong
who lived in Chuncheon as well.
- Here.
- Thank you.
So you are my husband's
hometown friend?
Yes. I just met with Dae Chul now,
and he told me he had a store here.
I came to buy one for myself.
Is that so? How thoughtful.
Take your time looking
at this catalog, then.
Thank you.
Let's see.
There are a lot of models.
By the way, you are quite amazing.
I am?
What for?
Raising someone else's child isn't
as easy...
as it sounds.
It's not something anyone can do.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to hide it from me.
I know it all.
Dae Chul felt awfully sorry to you.
A daughter of yours had
cardiac surgery,
and you had to raise
a stranger's child.
He felt so guilty about it.
He even told you about that?
You two must be really close.
Of course.
You must have gone through a lot.
What could I have done?
I didn't give birth to the child,
but she is still my husband's child.
I had to raise the child well.
It's so nice and warm.
It's so nice to have one gifted...
after only selling it.
What is this?
Why is this here?
You have
such a great hometown friend.
What?
Your friend bought this for us.
I don't have any hometown friends.
What do you mean?
You seemed so close.
And a friend with no secrets.
I'm talking about Mr. Koo Chun Soo,
your friend.
What?
Director Cha.
Are you working late on your own?
That's so hardworking of you.
I've signed it, so take a look
and go home.
Okay. Thank you.
Sure.
Mind your own business.
Dad!
This man is...
It's Yu Jung's family.
I'm sorry?
Woman, get up here.
So you told Chun Soo about Yu Jung?
Why are you yelling at me?
You were the one who told him first.
What?
He already knew about everything.
That Yu Ra had cardiac surgery...
and that Yu Jung was a child
you brought with you.
Mr. Koo knew everything
and told me about it.
What?
He knew about it?
What did you just say now?
I was brought from somewhere else?
What do you mean by that?
(A Man in a Veil)
You had an affair behind Mom's back?
Why did you give birth to me?
It'd have been better if you didn't!
Why did you lie to me?
What lie?
Is Ms. Han the child from then?
Would this help in finding
my lost past?
Haven't you thought of a way
to deal with Seo Ji Sook yet?
There's a way.
I don't care. I'll do anything
as long as the two don't meet.
Han Yu Jung and Han Yu Ra.
The two were sisters?
Yu Ra, let's get a divorce.
I found something
to hold you responsible for.
What do you think?