(This drama is fictional and all characters, organizations,)
(and events are unrelated to historical events.)
If you don't want to talk about it,
why don't we come up with our own hand signals?
Like this one.
What is that?
This means whatever I'm saying is a lie.
What do you think? It's not that hard.
A king never lies.
(Episode 15)
What kind of sin could such a young child commit?
I smell liquor and something else.
She didn't drink poison.
I cannot believe she was forced to drink poison with such small hands.
Her hands are warm. She's still alive.
Please get up.
Dam Hyang!
Your Highness.
- Sir. - You are here.
Sir.
Here you go.
We must not leave such a young child in the mountains.
I would only feel comfortable if I held a funeral for her.
- Goodbye, then. - Goodbye.
How's Dam Hyang. Is she okay?
She should have left the Palace safely by now.
I pardoned her mother, who was a government slave,
and made the preparations so she could leave Hanyang with her.
She's meeting her mom.
She was so worried about her as she only had four fingernails.
Thank goodness. This is great.
How did you do it? Did you use a sleeping pill?
I had her drink mafeisan.
Mafeisan is what the noted doctor Hua Tuo used for surgeries, right?
You have heard of him.
Of course. I've read "Three Kingdoms for Kids" so many times.
"Three Kingdoms for Kids"?
You. You should've told me about your plan beforehand.
It was an urgent situation,
and it was dangerous for many people to know.
Did you hear from Special Director Hong?
Yes. He made sure that the child escaped safely.
Good job.
It was reckless to put yourself in such danger...
over a court maid.
She was not just a court maid.
If I gave up on this child,
it would become easier to give up on...
10, 100, and then all of my people.
I thought Cheoljong was just a fool,
but he was an incredibly stupid fool.
Don't spend too much time thinking about great things.
You won't live long.
My goal is not to live an embarrassing life.
Those are perfect values to have an early death.
This is all your...
This is how she is thanking me.
The language that the Queen uses is different from others.
That "Queen Dictionary" is useless.
It's filled with liberal and mistranslations.
- Did you see it? - You left it open, so I could see.
But was the position of queen always this dangerous?
Why is everyone so determined to kill me?
I will prevent this from happening ever again.
No. I will take care of it my way.
The best defense is a good offense.
As of today, I'm the crazy one in this palace.
(Episode 15, The Crazy X in This Place)
Did you try to get rid of the Queen?
The Queen is on the King's side.
She gave our family's embarrassments and weaknesses to the King.
She has fallen for the King and turned her back on her family.
That is not true.
I am sure you do not want to believe...
that the Queen, whom you adore so much,
is nothing but a foolish woman...
who flounders about after falling for a man.
After I came into this family,
I did whatever you wanted so that you would accept me.
It was not just so that I could remain in this household.
I wanted to become like you...
and respect you.
However, the moment you tried to hurt the Queen,
you are no longer my father.
If anyone tries to harm the Queen,
I will be sure to slit their throats.
You can come back home whenever you want.
Even if you do not consider me to be your father,
you will always be my son.
Who would've hidden the ledger in Daejojeon Hall?
The prime suspects...
are the two people who have a grudge against me for no reason.
Queen Dowager Jo and Jo Hwa Jin.
If you consider motive, the culprit is Jo Hwa Jin.
Considering how she acted during the hunting game on Surit-nal, I'm sure.
However, Jo Hwa Jin didn't come near Daejojeon Hall recently.
If you consider movement, Queen Dowager Jo is the culprit.
Here.
It's suspicious how she comes here so often these days.
Of course, Queen Dowager Jo also has a clear motive.
Is it the Queen Dowager?
That little raccoon.
Then how did the Queen Dowager get her hands on the ledger?
That's the mystery.
But more than that, what kind of ledger is it?
I did not have an exorcism today.
I apologize for my rude behavior previously.
I am sure you would not bow your head for no reason.
What is the reason?
As I had expected,
you are quick to read the situation.
Thank you for joining me in this uncomfortable gathering.
I am sure you came to realize from today's events,
It is the time for the nobility to live,
not our families.
We are intimately interdependent.
(Literally says "without lips, teeth are cold" and means they're close.)
If 1 of the 2 family ends up in ruins,
the other family will have a hard time staying afloat.
That is why I would like to suggest a decree of amnesty...
as a promise of harmony between our two families.
(Granting amnesty for certain criminals for their crimes)
A decree of amnesty?
Many wasted talents lost their government posts...
due to a momentary mistake in both of our families.
That is why we should make a decree of amnesty to pardon those people.
In other words, it is a symbol of our promise,
and a congratulatory gift.
What do you think?
Would you like to join me in this goal?
The Ministry of War tried to play dirty tricks to fulfill his greed,
and I am also guilty for being unable to subdue him.
As a result, I, Kim Jwa Geun,
request to step down from my post as Training Commander.
Things will not be over for me.
As long as I am breathing.
Eat slowly.
Do you have enough side dishes?
If I had any sense of shame, I would not be able to eat.
Why on earth did you run away?
I believe I treated you well until now.
The thing is...
Mother?
Mother.
Goodness.
You have been through so much, Dam Hyang.
It is okay.
It will all be okay.
We must try to smile around her.
Her Highness must not...
stay sad for a long time.
Yes, ma'am.
Your Highness. It is time for you to wake up.
Your Highness.
Were you unable to get any sleep last night?
I am worried that you may put a strain on your body.
I have a lot on my mind, so I couldn't get any sleep.
By the way, they probably slept just fine, right?
Who?
The people who tried to mess me up.
That will be the last night they sleep without trouble.
I hope they had a good night's sleep.
- Court Lady Choi. - Yes.
Send someone to my father...
and ask him to come to the palace now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Your father is here.
Already?
I was just about to request your attendance at the palace.
But you were already on your way.
Yes.
It seems to me I made the right decision to come.
- The other day... - The other day...
You can go first.
No. You can go first.
No. You can go first, Father.
- I am sorry about the other day. - I am sorry about the other day.
- No. I should apologize first. - No. I must apologize first.
- I should. - No, I should.
- Gosh. - I should.
Gosh. Blood is thicker than water.
Right.
Well, I asked to see you here today...
because of the ledger.
- Did you know about this? - Everyone is going crazy over it.
What is the ledger for?
The ledger has records of our clan's illegal activities.
A weakness of the Andong Kim clan.
That's why Cheoljong wanted to get his hands on that.
I actually came here today, so I could talk about the ledger.
After you and the King stayed at my house, the ledger disappeared.
So I have been suspecting the King all this time.
But a while ago,
a trusted and cherished slave of mine ran away.
Luckily, I caught him and asked why he ran away.
The day before the ledger went missing,
he let in Royal Noble Consort Eui.
When things were chaotic at home,
he thought he must have caused trouble and ran away. So...
I am sorry, Your Highness.
It is not your fault.
Now,
I have completed the puzzle.
Pardon?
Sunwon was the architect behind my assassination.
I have specially prepared...
ice which is more precious than gold today.
The Queen Dowager indirectly bullied me.
I will serve you my food some time...
I must eat it now.
And Jo Hwa Jin is the one who provided the ammunition.
You should come clean to the King.
You are threatening me.
I heard you...
loud and clear.
Father, I have someplace to be right now.
Where?
To open the door to the fiery pit.
I'll make you regret for messing with me.
She used to be as docile as a sika deer.
She has become ferocious over a short period of time here.
I know that parents cannot be impartial to their children.
But a sika deer?
If I were to compare her to an animal,
she would be a wild horse.
My daughter is a wild horse?
The tattoo of the Maori people.
The feather from a peacock.
And the devil wearing Prada.
Strength is beauty.
Today, I'll be wearing the most beautiful armor.
What do you think?
Good.
Revenge is sweet when served with fireworks.
What is this?
What you see is not everything.
To find out what is inside,
I must cut it in half.
I thought it was just a potato like it seemed.
You completely deceived me.
One should not throw away trust and cut it without a good reason.
One should make sure what it is before cutting it.
Because once it is done, one cannot take it back.
I will serve the drinks now.
I prepared brunch today...
because I wanted to return the favor for preparing...
such a lovely brunch the other day.
The cool drink from the last brunch was truly amazing...
that I would not have noticed anything even if someone was dead.
Please try it.
I am not thirsty.
I put a lot of effort into it. Please at least have a sip.
I said I did not want to.
I went through an ordeal to prepare for that.
If you do not want to drink it...
Ice is better when you bite it.
A while back, I told you that...
I'd help you to stay healthy and young for the rest of your life.
And I will continue to do that.
If you start suspecting food, drinks and anything that goes on your body,
life will be nothing but misery.
Now that the regency had ended,
you must think you can do whatever you want.
Do you think...
you can still be the Queen without your clan?
Your Highness.
I don't rely on my clan or my husband.
I'm doing whatever I want because I know what I can.
Oh, right. Head Eunuch.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I have been neglecting my duty...
to produce an heir.
How could I be so neglectful of my duty as the King?
So go and report to her now.
Report to her?
I do not understand, Your Majesty.
You know you always report to her.
How dare you?
You have given me no choice but to punish you!
Your Majesty, I am sorry.
- Punish me with death. - What is wrong?
I was not speaking to you.
You hold the power of my life now.
I do not want that.
What will I do with that?
Please punish me with death, Your Majesty.
My goodness. I do not wish to have such power.
Head Eunuch, I know that you have no choice.
You must follow your orders.
I would rather have you get angry at me.
This is scarier.
How can you be a spy when you are scared so easily?
I have somewhere to go before the royal conference.
Go to Injeongjeon Hall.
My goodness, can you read it somewhere else?
Head Eunuch is in shock right now.
I hope you had a peaceful night.
Is that how you greet your elder?
The hairpieces are heavy.
So I cannot bow my head.
This is a sacred place where ancestral rites are performed.
It is not polite to wear such extravagant garments.
You have to preen yourself before asking for a refund.
Oh, I'm so forgetful.
I forgot to offer incense to the late King.
I can't believe I disgraced Chunghak-dong School of Etiquette.
Stop it.
I'm extremely faithful to Confucianism.
I can't stand not performing the ritual.
I told you to not touch it.
You left something in my room.
You came unannounced and invaded my privacy.
In the end, it was that.
What are you doing?
I told you. A refund.
I should return the nonsense I had to go through.
What kind of rudeness is this?
Slandering your elder carelessly...
and complaining so hard.
You have always been like that,
but your attitude is even more insolent today.
Is it because you grew up without a mother?
You mother-in-law.
If I'm rude because I grew up without a mother,
are you rude because you lived without your child?
It's hot.
I'm so mad that I can't stand how hot it is.
The portrait of your precious son...
almost burnt.
You lost your mind.
Yes, I lost it big time.
I think I'm the best among all the girls who lost their minds.
So watch out.
If you touch even a strand of my hair,
you will never see your son's face again.
It is not the Queen I should have worried about.
It was other people.
"The best defense is a good offense."
Oh, my. I didn't see you were here.
I can't believe how weak your presence is.
I'm trying to skip a stone. Would you like to join me?
Do it by yourself.
The ledger.
You took it.
Thanks to the ledger, I almost died.
Tell me.
Is that what you wanted?
Did you really not kill O Wol?
No matter what I say, you believe what you want to believe.
I have to take the King away from you,
kill O Wol and put her in the well.
Because it will make me a bad girl who deserves to die...
and make you a kind and poor victim.
This is why victim playing is scary.
Because you're slowly turning into a monster every day,
without even realizing it.
Look at the mirror.
And see how ugly you are.
Hold it yourself to come up.
I don't feel like being too kind right now.
When I fell into the lake in front of you,
you perhaps...
could hold me.
This proves...
that I'm a better person than you.
Kim Jwa Geun, the former Training Commander,
resigned.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The impeachment process was delayed,
so you all could have taken responsibility for that.
It is a pity.
Oh, it was slip of the tongue.
I wanted to say it is fortunate.
The next agenda is...
Today, there is something I want to declare to you before that.
I will make an office to remove the indictment of the Three Tax System.
Its name is Samjung Ijungchung.
Samjung Ijungchung?
It will establish legislation...
and develop detailed plans to solve the fundamental issues...
to remedy the problems of the Three Tax System.
Joseon depends on agriculture.
The country can prosper only when its farmers prosper.
Government officials' exploitation against farmers...
is an act to threaten the foundation of the country,
hence it will be punished as high treason.
A careful examination is required to make a new office.
You should hear our opinions first before...
I accept no compromise to do the right thing.
It means your opinions...
do not matter any longer.
Also, I will give the late King Sunjong...
the posthumous name of Sunjo according to the rules.
The King is more aggressive than usual today.
Your Majesty.
There is a new appointment today.
Chief Royal Secretary also makes a slip of the tongue.
It should be an appointment proposal.
The position of Minister of War is vacant now.
A weak military equates to a crisis of the empire.
Therefore, I urge you to appoint the Minister of War...
through the Border Defense Council now.
Come in Minister of War.
Kim Byeong In, the Minister of War, wishes to...
offer his greetings.
Kim Byeong In can be a threat as he has the Jo clan's support.
Both clans...
have petitioned for amnesties because...
That must be his doing as well.
I doubt we can ignore this many appeals.
This might give the upper class an excuse for an uprising.
Now that you have full control,
you can do whatever you want.
But it is still hard to stop them from going against you.
The best defense is a good offense.
Now, it is a matter of...
hitting the target faster than our opponent.
We do not have time to recruit more people.
I want you to oversee Ijungchung.
Special Director Hong, I will officially dispatch you...
to visit the three cities in the South...
as people are distressed there and launch an investigation.
Another business trip?
Do this for me.
The more time passes by, you two stay here and give orders.
I feel like I am doing all the heavy lifting by myself. Am I wrong?
No, you are not alone. I always...
Once you are done with this investigation,
- I could give you a few days off. - I will get ready for my trip.
"I could."
I said I could.
I doubt that he heard that.
That fool.
Your Majesty.
You have a letter, Your Majesty.
I will not harm you. Come closer.
The Queen has sent a letter to Your Majesty.
Are you sick?
You are so fragile.
Revenge is something else. I thought I would be elated.
It was exhilarating.
What a thrill.
His Majesty is...
You're here.
You seem especially more beautiful today.
That suits you well.
Everything looks good with a pretty face.
So anything looks good on me.
Who knew I would make a great queen?
I can never get used to that.
I asked to see you,
so we can form an alliance.
My clan probably left me, thinking I am on your side.
So I've got nothing to lose.
If you are on my side,
your clan will become your enemy.
The clan ditched me first.
So I'll ditch my clan now.
If we have the same enemy, doesn't that make us allies?
Yes.
Starting now, the no-touching rule does not apply between us.
Sure. No more no-touching rule.
In martial arts movies,
I saw they drip their blood in a cup and drink it together.
But I can't do something like that as it's unsanitary.
Let's drink tea and celebrate our alliance.
It will be nice and simple.
What...
Is this what allies do?
Yes. This is how it's done.
- Bottoms up. - What...
Now that we're allies, let's clear the air.
Why did you try to kill me?
Right.
It is a topic we must discuss at some point.
We thought you heard our conversation...
about assassinating your father.
He is still your father-in-law.
To me, he was one of the corrupted officials.
You are so harsh.
I get it. You even tried to kill your own wife.
You're a serial killer of the Kims.
I am sorry.
I know that my apology does not mean much now,
but there were many misunderstandings and situations.
Okay.
Then, you owe me one.
I won't forgive you until you pay me back somehow.
So what are you trying to achieve?
Strengthening the sovereign authority?
That is only a tool to fix our broken empire.
I do not think the root of the world can change.
So to be honest, I like your tool, rather than your goal.
If the sovereign authority is strengthened, I'll be strong too.
Then, no one can come after me.
I am well aware of the fear that comes from a death threat.
I know you are acting tough, but you must be scared.
I'm not sure.
Is it because I died once?
I hate being trampled on more than dying.
If I can chew out all those people trying to trample on me,
I will die with a smile.
Your Highness.
It is time to prepare lunch.
Okay. On that note,
I'll go do that.
I will die with a smile.
"Die with a smile".
- Lord Kim. - Hey. Byeong In.
I mean, Minister of War.
- Are you teasing me? - Gosh, no.
Please call me by my name.
Actually, I was waiting for you...
because I wanted to talk about the Queen with you.
As it so happens, I had something to tell you about her as well.
Where did I put it?
- Hold on. - I saw it.
You!
How dare you use the knife? You have not been here long enough.
Things are different now.
Chef these days never want to drink some makgeolli after work.
They always say no. My goodness.
I said it would be my treat. I do not know why they say no.
Goodness.
I do not understand the court maids these days.
I told them to come late, and they really came late.
They should have been there before their scheduled time.
- Kids these days. - Kids these days.
This is for Tongmyeongjeon Hall.
Darn it.
I had one more revenge left.
A recipe for revenge?
I should do exactly what he did to me, right?
A tooth for a tooth. An eye for an eye.
A loss of manhood for a loss of manhood.
Then, brackens?
- Adlay? - Brackens and adlay.
This recipe has a lot of healthy ingredients.
It will take forever to achieve my goal with food.
That's too long of a plan.
Let's go big.
- Castration. - Castration?
I have never heard...
Oh, I see.
It is such a precious ingredient.
I am not here to burden you.
I am a man who knows when to give up.
I apologize.
You do not need to.
May I ask you a question for the last time?
- Yes. - Why do you...
dislike a man who has ambition?
While living in the Palace, I have seen many ambitious people...
and their difficult ends.
I do not like...
and am afraid of such things.
Thank you for answering my question.
If I could dare expect something from you,
it is that your bright smile...
will remain forever.
Oh, it is you.
It must be over.
Your intuition is as sharp as a sickle.
You are so quick-witted.
How could I not know when you are crying like this?
Do not look at me.
I do not want anyone to see me like this.
Then go over there and cry on your own.
People might think that I made you cry.
It was not me.
I will not cry anymore.
Being able to end my feelings cleanly is a part of love.
It may be harder than continuing to love her.
You have become quite the poet.
Let us go. Stop crying.
She insisted on sending me a meal?
What is with this ominous drawing?
Goodness, it is so pretty.
Court Lady Chun. You would survive even after consuming poison...
because you are so slow-witted.
Why are you complimenting me all of a sudden?
Your Highness.
I, Shim Ong of the Han clan, am here to say hello.
Have we not met before?
I am much obliged.
No, I mean... Please forgive me.
I believe you should be saying something else to me.
For example,
"Punish me with death, Your Highness".
I lost all the popcorn I worked so hard to make because of you.
I lost it all because it went flying.
I had no idea you were the Queen,
and I committed such a huge crime.
You had no idea it was me?
Then why did you run away?
That is because...
such a noble person was running after me,
so I was surprised.
I did not have any other reasons.
Is that so?
To be honest, I called you here...
to give you a government post.
It is a good position. You don't need to worry about getting fired,
and the pay is good too.
Of course, you end up losing something else.
Pardon?
Did you just say I would lose something?
When I saw you, despite it being a brief meeting,
your physiognomy is perfect for this position.
I am much obliged, Your Highness.
You...
should become my eunuch.
What?
Hold on. Wait a second.
Let go of me, you eunuchs.
Your Highness.
I beg your kindness.
Thank you for your boundless generosity.
Why are you doing this to me?
First,
you bought a fake family register and pretended to be a noble.
No. This isn't your fault.
The social structure that divides classes is to blame.
That is correct.
Let's go again. First,
you put poisonous herbs in the water of the Royal Kitchen...
and ruined the King's banquet.
Second,
your descendant is a bad person.
"My descendant"?
Are you sure you did not mix it up with my ancestors?
No.
I'm certain.
Your descendant is a bad person.
My descendant?
Your Highness.
If I become a eunuch, I will not have any descendants.
If I become a eunuch, I will not have any descendants. Your Highness!
I will not have any descendants.
Hey, do you have any descendants? You do not, right?
I will not be able to have any descendants!
My gosh. Your Highness!
Your Highness, the Ministry of War is here.
Your Highness,
The Andong Kim clan.
I'm certain they're all in cahoots.
But my father is also a part of the Andong Kim clan.
What? I just naturally called him "my father".
The transfer of emotions is serious.
I figured out what had happened to you after I met you yesterday.
I had no idea you went through such a big ordeal.
You had no idea...
that they tried to kill me?
I am not on my father's side, nor am I a part of the Kim clan.
However, you aren't free from either of them.
You will find out eventually.
Is he an enemy or an ally?
How dare he do that to So Yong?
Even still, how could he do that to the Queen?
Kim Jwa Geun, that jerk.
I ought to...
Furthermore, it's Samjung Ijungchung.
They're using the corruption of the leaders as an excuse...
to try to bring down our family.
Do not worry.
If they try to find a problem with it by calling it exploitation,
then nobody is innocent.
In order to protect themselves,
they will all try to protect the leaders,
so all that will be left of Samjung Ijungchung is its shell.
Even if you join them temporarily,
do not even blink in front of Queen Dowager Jo.
She may smile in front of you,
but she is always ready to stab you in the back.
I will keep that in mind.
Court Lady Chun.
Yes, Your Highness.
Clear the table and call in Nurse Park.
Are you already done eating?
I don't have much of an appetite.
I heard that you were quite satisfied...
with the meals that the Queen prepared for you.
It was not that great.
It was just edible.
The Queen is very heartbroken.
She said that Royal Noble Consort Eui came between you,
and she was mistaken to believe that our family turned our backs on her.
She is blaming herself.
Royal Noble Consort Eui?
I heard it from the Queen's father today.
The person that deceived you was not the Queen.
It was Royal Noble Consort Eui.
The King is here.
Tell him to come in.
Your Majesty.
I apologize for coming at such a late hour without any notice.
It is okay.
It is an honor regardless of when you come.
I came to tell you something.
What is it?
It is about the body of the court made found in the well recently.
The Queen Dowager hired someone to do that.
Queen Dowager did it?
Why would she...
Can you not think of the reason either?
If so, the body is...
It must not be O Wol's.
It is impossible. It was definitely O Wol.
I heard it was difficult to identify due to the condition of the body.
Why were you sure that it was O Wol?
She was wearing a garment for court maid,
and O Wol was the only court maid who had disappeared.
She knew that you would think she is O Wol.
What the Queen Dowager wants...
is you relying on her.
But why did it have to be the well of all?
I told her what I had gone through in the well.
The well is a place where I met you.
But it is also a place that hurt me.
It reminded me of you,
so I was sure I lost the person I cherished.
Now I realize I cannot carelessly reveal my wound to others...
in the palace.
Drag the Queen down to the nightmare I am living in.
You should never trust the Queen Dowager from now on.
We should hide that we know it,
so do not let her know that you know what she did.
I am also deeply disappointed and feel betrayed by her.
The well is a place...
that instills fear in me.
I cannot believe she used it.
It's similar to poker and hwatu.
Gabbling and gaming...
are surely the best ways to waste your time and life.
I am glad to hear that.
We were worried you might have a hard time because of Dam Hyang.
Please forgive me.
Don't worry. Dam Hyang went to a good place.
Right? She must have gone to a good place, right?
Dam Hyang.
I mean... A really good place.
Yes, Your Highness.
Dam Hyang...
I said she really went to a good place.
Why are you crying?
My apologies.
Come to think of it,
I couldn't even say farewell to her.
Dam Hyang.
- Dam Hyang. - Your Highness.
Seven.
Eight.
This is...
called nine.
Please forgive me.
Darn it.
- Dam Hyang. - Dam Hyang.
All in.
How did Queen Dowager get the ledger?
The ledger we tried so hard to find but failed.
At this point, would it not be the right choice to recruit her?
It is a joke.
Hearing she is better than me who can freely roam outside the palace,
I am disappointed in myself.
Queen Dowager mostly stays at Seonwonjeon Hall.
I cannot understand how she got the ledger.
The fact that she faked the corpse...
means she has people working for her.
Should we recruit them then?
Is the composite of the one with a goblin mask not available yet?
I have been too busy with work these days.
Freeing Dam Hyang's mother from slavery...
and finding her missing father.
You could not find her father though, did you?
How can I find a person who is hiding in the mountains?
He must have become a bandit.
Thinking about the holiday...
after the business trip as a royal investigator,
I am barely enduring it these days.
Hey, what I meant was the holiday...
Can you appoint me...
as a secret inspector, not a royal investigator.
That is cooler.
After hiding my identity, I will show them the tablet, like this!
You are a born secret inspector. Do it as you want.
One more time.
I didn't think Great Lord Yeongeun was that kind of person.
Kim Jwa Geun is the one who deserves to die.
Great Lord Yeongeun is...
my only family.
Hey, are you sleeping after trying to kill...
your father-in-law and wife?
Oh, you're not.
Calm down, my heart.
It hurts my pride.
She was in the water for a long time.
How suffocating and painful must it have been?
Finding her body in the well is either an awful coincidence...
or someone is trying to come between us.
I was too deep in my thoughts.
You must have been deeply shocked.
The palace is too big for me.
Not only it makes you lonely, but it also makes you lost.
I found the court maid who sold the norigae you had given to O Wol.
She said she only found the norigae buried at the palace.
Is that so?
She is the very court maid who put the dead body in the well...
by Queen Dowager's order.
O Wol is alive.
She was attacked in the palace.
She could not even step foot outside the palace.
Do you not have to wish...
the dead body found in the well is not O Wol?
Do you not have to be happy...
that there is a possibility that it is not O Wol's dead body?
Why do you believe that the corpse is O Wol?
What on earth...
What on earth are you hiding?
Last time,
what did you hand over...
to the Queen Dowager?
Did you see it?
I...
can see nothing without your permission.
Anyone can be lost sometimes.
You still have a chance to get back on track.
What if I am not lost just for a moment?
Can I still...
get back on track?
I cannot go back.
Your Highness.
The dead body has to be O Wol.
Why are you making samhyang ramyeon...
in the middle of the night?
Why do you crave ramyeon especially at night?
You know it will make your face puffy the next morning.
Yet it's so hard to fight the temptation.
You worked hard but it is a shame that there is not a chance.
Grand Queen Dowager does not eat...
late at night.
So instead of her, let me...
No.
You should have told me that you came.
Why did you just stand there knocking on the door?
Do you want to have ramyeon before you go?
What is ramyeon? And where do you want me to go?
No pressure. It's just a kind of research.
Or a test.
No. I shouldn't do this.
But if it's just a bite...
No, no.
Ramyeon has such an addictive taste.
Once you start eating it, you can't stop.
What are you doing?
An inner conflict.
What would you do if it were you?
Do you think you're going to eat ramyeon or not?
I think I will explain what ramyeon is first.
- First, - First?
I will try it.
Right?
You know how it is only after you try it.
If it's just a one-time thing as I was drunk,
or if I have really gone mad,
or if this is...
real.
Are we speaking the same language right now?
Sure.
We're talking about the ramyeon.
Come closer. Ramyeon is the best when it's hot.
(Dongmongseonseup)
What are you doing with this?
Oh, my!
What should I do? This is such a precious book.
What do you think this is that you said it is precious?
Why is Dongmongseonseup precious to you?
It's...
Was it you?
The person who saved me. Was it you?
Did you save me from the well?
Yes.
It was me.
(Mr. Queen)
My Cheoljong will be desperately waiting for me to come.
Did you dig a trap?
I cannot believe the fight the Queen declared was real.
- Is it my turn? - Draw your sword.
If someone did not clean up after himself and leaves a trace,
he will have to take responsibility for everything.
Even though I removed the Kim clan,
Kim Byeong In is becoming more powerful.
I feel like there is no progress.
If Cheoljong makes it, the world 200 years later will change as well.
As long as I'm on your side, you will win.
I have a secret weapon.
I know the future.