(Episode 74)
You're asking for trouble,
aren't you?
Han Jae Soo!
Give me the will
when I'm asking you nicely.
I can't. I will never give it
to you.
Fine. You're already registered
as dead,
so you wouldn't have any regrets
if you die right now.
Yes, I don't have any regrets.
But I won't die in your hands.
Dae Ro!
You prick!
Dad.
You jerk.
What have you done to him?
Should I kill both you
and your dad together?
Dad.
You're messing with me
because of this will, aren't you?
Without this will,
how are you going to prove that
Han Jae Soo didn't kill Eok Shim?
You scumbag.
Tell me you'll hand over
Wonky Box Lunch.
Say it, you brat!
Dad.
Dae Ro.
Dad, are you all right?
I'm all right.
Are you all right?
- Yes.
- What about the will?
It's right here.
Can you walk?
Yes, let's hurry.
Let's go.
Okay, Dad.
- Are you really all right?
- Yes.
Goodness.
Where are we going to hide
that will?
I think we should hide it
in the office temporarily.
Okay.
Dae Ro.
Let's hide it here.
Let's put it there for now.
Oh, my.
What happened to your faces?
Did you hurt your hand too?
Is this Ma Chung Goo's doing?
Yes.
Why is he doing this to you
and Ms. Han?
He tried to steal Dad's sister's
will, so we struggled a bit.
What?
So what happened to the will?
Thankfully, we retrieved it.
But would he give up easily?
What if he comes here again?
I know. What are we going to do
if he makes a scene again?
Why don't we just sell the land
in Gurye and pay him back?
You'll be able to recover
your identity in 15 days.
So we just need to bear with it
until then.
You'll get punished if you sell
the land in her name.
Dear me.
Sir, are you all right now?
Yes. You guys got a fright, right?
Thank you for looking after
the company while I was gone.
But is it okay for you
to come back to work already?
I missed you guys so much
that I couldn't stay put.
Anyway,
did DBS confirm the cast list
and the host?
Don't get me started.
We proposed Hong Young Ja
as the host, but they refused.
What?
Then who do they want as the host?
I think they're trying to stop us
from producing the show.
What should we do?
Why those people!
They making my blood soar
as soon as I return to work.
Wouldn't it be difficult for them
to refuse Koo Hyun Moo as a host?
Right. He'd be great!
Let's get it confirmed!
But the problem is the guarantee.
Oh, Jun Soo promised
to invest in the company.
I'll ask him to fund the production
of "Marketaurant" as well,
so raise the guarantee right away.
Jun Soo will invest
in Na Production?
What?
Yes.
Welcome.
What are we here for?
Are you going to wear a hoodie
and sneakers to meet my parents?
I have heels and outfits.
Just buy them.
I want to buy them for you.
Don't you know that your lover
will run away if you buy them shoes?
Do you want me to wear these shoes
and be gone from your sight forever?
You're younger than me...
and a screenwriter,
but why are you so slow?
Don't you know people give you shoes
to walk the good path together?
Gosh, that's cheesy.
Hurry up and chose something
you like.
How about this ivory colored boots?
These stitches
make your legs look slimmer...
and the heels look unique too.
That looks good.
Try them on.
This way.
How do I look?
I kind of feel awkward.
They look pretty.
It suits you very well.
- Then we'll take this,
- Yes.
This loafer,
these sneakers,
and that loafer too.
Yes, sir.
Why would you buy so many shoes?
What am I? A centipede?
Wear them on proper occasions.
Stop wearing sneakers all the time.
I'll take this handbag too.
I can't even fit a laptop in there.
How am I going to use this tiny bag?
You could carry it at times
when you don't need a laptop.
Your boyfriend has such great taste.
You must be pleased.
Let's try this on.
Do you like sundae soup that much?
I didn't use to like it this much.
But I crave it these days.
Is that so?
Eat up.
Would you like to take some home?
This is enough.
I don't need to take it home.
Oh, right. Since you didn't want
to see the house with me,
I picked a house.
Here.
What do you think?
If you like it, I'll buy it.
How many square feet is this place?
It's about 158 or 165 square meters
or something.
Why do we need such a big house
when it's only the four of us?
You need a walk-in closet,
study room, and bedrooms.
Four people need about a house
of this size.
Even if I cancel
the pension insurance,
I can't fill up this huge house
with appliances.
Who asked you for that?
All I need is you.
Even though
it's a contractual marriage,
how can I go in empty-handed?
I'll just prepare what I can.
I said you don't need to.
I'll take care of everything.
Don't mind it, Ms. Shin.
Still, that's wrong.
Let's just start with two bedrooms.
Byeo Ri and I will take one,
and you can take the other.
What?
Are you leaving me out?
Fine, then. I'll compromise
and make it three bedrooms.
But...
if we tell them we'll be living with
Byeo Ri, your parents won't like it.
I'm worried about that.
You're not marrying my parents.
I told you it's okay.
What is there to worry about?
The stuff we bought is too heavy
for you to carry,
so I'll bring it over later
in the evening.
I'm not at home in the evening.
What? Why?
My grandfather wants
to have dinner with the family,
so I'm going there.
Is that so?
Byeo Ri will be alone.
Yes. I don't like that.
Then I can go over
and have dinner with Byeo Ri.
Have fun at your grandfather's.
Oh, I'm late.
Are you here to cook?
What?
What happened to your forehead?
You left early in the morning
without even making breakfast.
I slipped in the ice
and hit a telephone pole.
My whole body aches,
but I'm here to cook because of you.
Oh, my back.
Oh, here.
You surprised me!
Go away, old man!
Stay still, I'll put it on for you!
You shameless old man!
You're creeping me out! Go away!
What?
Are you being shy?
I don't like it...
when somebody touches me.
Go! I said go!
Dad.
What? Oh, Hae Shim, you're here.
I am.
Ms. Han, what's wrong?
Oh, she fell on the ice,
so I said I'd help put the patches
on, and she's making a big scene!
Oh, is that what that was?
Are you injured? Let me help
put the patches on.
No need for that.
I don't like it...
when people touch me.
I really don't like it.
I don't even like my own hands
touching my own body!
She's just weird. Leave her be!
Why are you here so early?
Our family is having dinner,
so of course, I should cook.
I see.
Oh, my goodness.
Isn't this Korean beef?
What? This is so expensive!
It was a gift.
I brought it,
so we could share it with you.
Who gave you such an expensive gift?
Just someone we know.
Ms. Han,
you must be in pain. Go rest.
No, I'm fine.
I've soaked the mung beans,
so I can make some pancakes,
japchae, salads...
That's too much trouble.
We can just grill the beef.
It's fine. Oh, my, it might get
cooked if you put it on top of that.
Your Wonky Box Lunch is here!
- It's Kim Bo Ra!
- Wow!
Can I have a picture?
Welcome, Ms. Kim!
What happened to your face?
Your hands are hurt too!
I got hurt while working.
You should be more careful.
What happened?
It's fine.
Oh, right. The comments on
"Here Comes Bo Ra" are really great.
The Weather Fairy Kim Bo Ra
is still quite popular.
I thought about it.
What do you think about continuing
"Here Comes Bo Ra" for a while?
Why don't you make your own channel
names "Here Comes Bo Ra"?
My own channel?
That's right.
We can call it a collaboration...
between Wonky Box Lunches
and Kim Bo Ra.
You can make your own channel
and communicate with your fans.
We can have you deliver
Wonky Box Lunches...
and promote our product.
It's a win-win for both of us.
That sounds good.
It's good to have a constant flow
of uploads in the beginning.
Then why don't we film
about twice a week?
Okay. Let's work together then.
Mr. Ma.
How did it go down with the will?
Don't even bring it up.
I have a cast on my arm
because of those jerks.
What?
That's why I said
I need hazard pay upfront.
If you don't pay me,
I'm taking my hand off the case.
What are you saying, Mr. Ma?
Come on.
My arm is messed up. What can I do?
I don't even have my guys.
There's no time. It's just one day
until tomorrow.
If you use more people,
will you make sure you handle it?
You can solve everything with money.
You're sure about this?
I'll start moving
as soon as you send me the money.
Chairperson, you called for me?
I did. Sit down.
Director Kim...
was confident that he would get
Wonky Box Lunch in the market.
Is this trustworthy news?
What?
I've never heard about it.
There's no reason for Kang Dae Ro
to hand over his company.
Then why...
did Director Kim say
such a ridiculous thing?
You said you were acquainted
with Kang Dae Ro, right?
Look into what happened discreetly.
Yes, I will.
Host Koo Hyun Moo said he'd do it
if the pay fits.
That's good.
DBS won't be able to nag at us
if he comes on board.
But CEO Na,
it looks like you made up
with Jun Soo all of a sudden.
He said he's giving us
financial support.
I almost died and came back,
so he feels bad.
That's why he's doing it.
It didn't look that simple.
Did you give Jun Soo and Ms. Shin
permission to get married...
in exchange for financial support?
Producer Um, you know the deal.
The more you try to separate them,
the more their longing will grow.
I gave permission for now,
and my wife said she'd separate them
using any means!
CEO Na!
How could you say allow it
so easily?
I shouldn't have stayed here.
I turned down DBS's scout offer
to stay.
I think...
I'm going to have to pack up.
My gosh!
Producer Um, don't be like that.
Who's going to work on
"Marketaurant"?
I planned it,
so I'll take it to DBS
and work on it.
I told you, I'm on your side.
We need to stick together,
even if it's just the two of us!
As long as you stay here,
I'll do my best
to get Jun Soo divorced...
and back with you.
Producer Um, you saved my life.
If it weren't for you,
I would have been dead already.
I'll make sure to keep my promise
to you somehow.
You're sure you can keep your word?
Of course.
Jun Soo.
Byeo Ri.
What's all this?
The shopping bags belong to Ah Ri,
and this is a cheese pork cutlet
for you.
This place is really popular.
I stood in line to get this.
Let's eat.
Wow, it looks delicious.
What did you get for Ah Ri?
Ah Ri and my parents
are meeting tomorrow...
to set the wedding date.
Those are the clothes and shoes
she's wearing to the meeting.
Byeo Ri, it's me!
It's Ms. Han!
- Grandma!
- Byeo Ri!
Hello.
I brought some food for Byeo Ri.
I thought she was alone.
Grandma, this is my brother-in-law.
You've never met, right?
The guy that looks like a goat?
I've seen him on television.
I've seen you on the show too.
Right. You were eating. Let's eat.
You should have dinner with us.
That's okay. I worked in front
of food all day, so I'm not hungry.
I'll put this in the fridge,
so you and Ah Ri can have it.
Don't give him any.
It seems like Mr. Kang and you
visit Ms. Shin's place often.
Why? Is something wrong with that?
No. I just heard from Ms. Shin
that you had a special connection.
How do you know her?
Don't go poking your nose
in everything.
Let's keep some distance.
I'm going to marry Ms. Shin.
I think this is something I can ask.
The truth is, Uncle Dae Ro
used to know my mom.
Really?
What about her?
Ms. Han is my friend.
Friend?
Don't you know what that is?
A friend?
It looks delicious.
When did you prepare all this food?
Ms. Han had it all prepared.
You must've been startled yesterday,
Father.
I'll make sure
to install a window guard.
You don't have to.
There is nothing to steal here.
Also, I have two young men
living here.
You don't need to worry.
I guess it's Ah Ri. Let me get that.
Hello, Grandpa. I'm Shin Ah Ri.
It's you. You came
for the shoot last time. Goodness.
I'm sorry I didn't introduce myself
that day.
I got some green tea.
You didn't have to.
Why don't you sit? Goodness.
We should've gathered for a meal
earlier.
I hope this is not too late.
I'm so glad that we could
all be here for a meal today.
Now then.
- You must be famished. Let's eat.
- Sure.
How old are you, Ah Ri?
I'm 29.
Really?
You're the same age as Bo Ra.
Ah Ri's birthday
comes three months before Bo Ra.
Are you dating anyone, Ah Ri?
Yes.
Are you not getting back? It's late.
I'll go after Byeo Ri goes to bed,
so you may go.
It's all right.
I'll go when Ms. Shin gets here.
I will take care of Byeo Ri.
You could get back now.
Goodness. You talk like you've
always been taking care of her.
We're going to live together.
I should get to know her.
Oh, my goodness.
Let's ask Byeo Ri then.
Byeo Ri.
Who do you want to stay with?
I like you...
as well as Jun Soo.
What's that?
But if you had to choose one,
who would it be?
Is it me or that goat?
Sorry?
It's hard for me to say.
If you want to stay longer,
please do.
You're putting her on the spot.
It's funny you should say that.
When did I put her on the spot?
Byeo Ri. You can say it.
It's okay if you say
you like me more.
But I really like you both.
Don't you like me a bit more?
You're back so early.
What about Byeo Ri?
Na Jun Soo was there
to give her dinner.
I know what he's like.
He came over to care for Byeo Ri?
He was acting proudly saying
that he's her brother-in-law.
My goodness. What an eyesore.
"What is your relationship
with Byeo Ri for you to come here?"
He was being so inquisitive
that I was dumbfounded.
Won't we have to live with Byeo Ri
when Ms. Shin gets married?
Of course.
Even if it would hurt Ms. Shin,
we should take her in.
Even if she insists on keeping
Byeo Ri, I won't let that happen.
I can't let her live in the house
of my enemy's son.
What do we do if Ms. Shin
refuses to let her go?
Then I'll have
to tell her the truth...
that I am Byeo Ri's dad.
Drinking this green tea
after eating beef...
gets rid of the greasiness.
It's so refreshing.
I'm glad you like it.
Grandpa is a picky eater.
The green tea you brought
is delicious.
You did.
By the way,
Ah Ri is dating someone, right?
Come to think of it,
she's at that age.
Do you have plans to get married?
Since you mention it,
the parents on both sides...
are meeting tomorrow
ahead of her marriage.
Is that so?
That's great news.
Excuse me.
I have to go to the bathroom.
What? Okay.
Well, then.
What does Ah Ri's boyfriend
do for a living?
Why won't you tell me?
Should it be kept confidential?
It's nothing like that.
It's CEO Na Jun Soo of Daybreak.
Na Jun Soo?
Are you saying...
Ah Ri is the reason
that Bo Ra got dumped?
Dad, it's not like that.
What do you mean it's not?
Bo Ra made a mistake on air
because of that jerk.
That's why she went off the grid
and ran away from home.
How hurt must've she been
to do such a thing?
That's a misunderstanding.
I heard it from Bo Ra herself.
She told me that Na Jun Soo
would make a good husband.
So I even told her
to invite him home.
But you're going
to let him marry Ah Ri?
How could you be so harsh
to Bo Ra as her parents?
I...
That's not what it is.
Joong Han.
I thought you love Bo Ra dearly.
How could you let this happen?
Is this because Ah Ri
is your daughter...
and Bo Ra is not your own?
Dad. That's not true.
Please calm down.
Shut it.
You're her mother.
How could you let the man
that Bo Ra loves marry Ah Ri?
Are you in your right mind?
Relax, Grandpa.
My love for Jun Soo was one-sided.
He likes Ah Ri, not me.
You don't need to lie to me.
I don't approve of this marriage!
That jerk hurt Bo Ra.
How could I let him be
part of our family?
I can't let that happen.
Dad.
Ah Ri...
is pregnant with Jun Soo's baby.
What did you say?
(No Matter What)
Tell me!
You knew about this, Dae Ro.
Didn't you?
Don't be anxious.
I will protect you.
Are you saying that you'll move out?
Are you trying to give her
a hard time living with the in-laws?
I heard you're meeting
your future in-laws today.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you earlier.
Does Director Kim Won Tae
have something on you?
Check that out.
Hey, Han Jae Soo.