(Episode 15)
I'm here.
Dad.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Soo Ho.
I thought I'd never get the chance...
to tell you that.
It's all right.
Dad, you should eat.
Here.
I promised...
to buy you something delicious.
You can once you've fully recovered.
Buy me something delicious.
(Alarm: 3am)
(Boarding Pass)
(Girlfriend)
Weren't you asleep? It's after midnight there.
I was studying, of course. It'll soon be our senior year.
- Are you at the airport? - Not yet.
I'll go once I see my father get discharged from the hospital.
Will he be returning to Korea too?
No, I'll be returning first.
He shouldn't travel long distances yet,
so he decided to take it easy for a while.
I see.
Anyway, it's been a month since we saw each other.
You're right.
I missed you.
- I'll meet you at the airport. - Don't.
I'll head to you as soon as my plane lands.
I'll see you tomorrow... No, I'll see you later.
Sure.
(Intensive Care Unit)
(Operation Room)
Dad?
Dad!
There was secondary bleeding in his brain,
so I had to perform emergency surgery.
The location of the bleeding isn't as ideal as it was last time,
but we're doing our best.
(Operating Room)
Your father had a cardiac arrest during the operation.
Fortunately, his life was never at risk.
His vitals are stable, but his condition is still serious.
(Arrivals)
- The divine Tae Hoon. - The mighty Hyun Kyu.
- Here's to another good year. - Likewise.
You're better looking...
Ju Kyung, are you in this class too?
- Talk about a deja vu. - I know.
Here's to another good year together.
- 1, 2, 3, go. - Go!
- I'm Yoo Tae Hoon. - And I'm Ahn Hyun Kyu.
Jjoo!
- You're here. - Hey.
I heard that Soo Jin dropped out of school during the break.
What? For real?
Rumor has it that she went to study abroad.
Are you all right though?
Did Soo Ho tell you when he'd be back?
No, not yet.
Why am I shivering?
How is he?
He's still unwell.
Did you get some sleep?
Ju Kyung, aren't you going to school?
- My stomach. - Ju Kyung!
What's wrong?
My goodness, what's the matter? Where does it hurt?
- My stomach. - Your stomach?
My goodness gracious.
Oh, dear. My goodness.
Does it hurt a lot?
(Girlfriend)
(Boyfriend)
Hey, Soo Ho.
Hello, ma'am.
Hello. Have you been well?
Yes, I guess.
But why didn't Ju Kyung pick up?
She's sick, so she's at the hospital right now.
She's sick? What's wrong with her?
Don't get startled. It's nothing to worry about.
She had an upset stomach.
She's a senior now, so she's been busy studying.
I think that caused her to get a little stressed.
Can she talk on the phone right now?
I'm sorry. She's asleep.
By the way, how's your father?
He's still not doing very well.
You must be having a hard time as well.
I'll tell Ju Kyung to call as soon as she wakes up.
Okay.
Hey, Soo Ho.
I feel like we haven't talked in ages.
I know, right? Is everything okay?
Yes, everything's okay.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
I finally got my license.
Good job.
I know, right?
- Ju Kyung. - Yes?
I think we should...
break up.
What?
I don't know when my dad's going to wake up.
And I'm sure it's hard for you to wait for me until I return.
What are you talking about?
I'm totally fine.
I can wait. I'm fine.
I just feel so bad.
I'm can't be there for you.
And that makes me feel so sorry.
So...
Who says you need to feel sorry?
I told you I'm fine. Why are you overreacting?
I don't want to break up.
You can even stay there forever. I'll save up and visit you instead.
I can't let you do that.
Why not?
Don't skip school.
Don't wait for me to call you anymore.
And sleep well.
Don't say that. Please don't.
Don't talk as if this is going to be our last phone call.
I'm going to pretend like I didn't hear anything.
I never picked up, okay?
(Prince Comics)
Mr. Prince.
Hey, Ju Bal.
Why are you throwing the chair out?
They're too old, so I'm going to change them.
Come inside.
Ta-da! I bought these with the money I earned.
They're a matching set.
Cute, right?
I'm not a crybaby. I'm Lee Soo Ho.
When will you finally remember me?
On the first day of snow, I'm going to go to Namsan...
and make a wish hoping that you'll remember me.
What?
You should've told me.
How was I supposed to know when you didn't tell me?
You know how they say your wish comes true on the first day of snow?
That means everyone who sees the first snow should be happy.
But why are there so many unhappy people in this world?
My dad still doesn't have a job.
I can't believe you believe that.
I'm sure they say that for a reason.
I thought about it long and hard.
I think the only person whose wish comes true...
is the very first person that the snow hits.
That's nonsense.
So when it snows for the very first time this year,
I'm going to go to the highest place...
and be the first one to touch the snow.
The highest place? Where?
- Are you going to get on a plane... - I'm going to go to Namsan.
What?
Isn't that the highest place in Seoul?
Let's say you're right.
You just wait and see.
If my wish comes true, you'll find out I was right.
(I'm not a crybaby. I'm Lee Soo Ho.)
(When will you finally remember me?)
(On the first day of snow, I'm going to go to Namsan...)
(and make a wish hoping that you'll remember me.)
I can't believe he remembered everything I said.
(On the first day of snow, I'm going to go to Namsan...)
(and make a wish hoping that you'll remember me.)
Why does he have to be so smart?
(College Scholastic Ability Test)
I took the CSAT today.
If I do well in the practical section,
I may be able to go to the college I want.
So this is how it feels to get closer to my dream.
I'm excited and happy.
Did you start studying music there?
Someday,
somewhere,
it'll be nice to hear music that you create.
I kept texting you to whine about how hard things were,
but now that the CSAT is over, I've lost that excuse.
Soo Ho. It's snowing here.
I hope it's warm...
and not cold where you are.
I won't contact you anymore.
Goodbye.
Okay. Smile, Chen.
You're so pretty.
- Nice. - Look at her.
Fix your hair a little.
You look so pretty.
Nice.
Please touch up her hair and makeup.
Here.
- Mouthwash. - Okay.
Mist.
- I'll spray it. - Okay.
Hey, Ju Kyung. When will you...
introduce me to Seo Jun?
He's a trainee, so he's too busy...
to meet anyone.
Don't you see him more often at the agency?
There are just so many times I can hit on him.
It hurts my pride too much.
I hear you're close friends. Let me meet with him alone.
- Ask him now while we're at it. - Now?
- Now? - Yes. Please? Please.
I'm begging you. Please?
Hold on. Just a minute.
She begs every time I see her.
Meet with her just once. Please? I'll treat you to a barbecue.
No, no. It's too annoying.
All you have to do is eat one meal with her.
Ju Kyung.
What did Seo Jun say?
Well... He must be busy. He isn't responding.
No. I detest her type.
- Oh no. - What's wrong?
- Oh no! - This is a designer dress.
- This was borrowed. - Oh no.
- You should've been careful. - No, I...
I know.
I told you to make sure not to get anything on the dress!
Seriously. What do we do?
I'm sorry. Sorry.
You can't pay for this even if you work for a year.
What will you do?
- It won't come out. - Oh no.
Ju Kyung. Talk to Seo Jun for me,
okay?
It's okay. It's okay, guys.
I'll talk to my agency about it. Just let me change.
- It feels icky. - Thank you.
- What an angel. - Let's go.
Don't scold her too much.
It's so icky.
Icky.
Cheers!
- Saebom High! - Yes!
Why doesn't she just seduce him if she likes him?
Why is she bugging me so much?
You said she's a witch, so a staff member quits every month.
If Seo Jun would just go on one date with Chen,
it would make your work life easier.
Why can't he do that for you?
I can't force him against his will. That's wrong.
But it's so hard for me.
Hey. Why did you call us out today?
I'm supposed to watch a movie with my Mini Me.
Isn't that right, wifey?
"Isn't that right, wifey?"
Yes, hubby.
Must you do that in front of your single friends?
What's wrong? Did the girl you were seeing dump you again?
I was not!
What? Are you happy that I'm single?
Are you not over me after dumping me?
Whatever. Dream on.
Listen! The reason I called all of you here today...
is to make a big announcement.
- What is it? - What the...
- So... - What is that?
Hyun Kyu and I are going to the army next month.
- What? - What?
- Where? - When?
We're going to enter together side by side. So please...
support us.
- Salute! - Salute!
Salute!
I'm sorry.
I didn't enlist.
I got a girlfriend.
- No way! - Oh my gosh.
A girl has taken ownership of my heart recently.
Regardless, I can't join the army.
I'm stunned. Of all the... I'm stunned.
You traitor! We agreed to join together!
- Hey! - Hey.
How can I leave my girlfriend as soon as I finally get one?
Give me a break. I knew it when I saw you didn't cut your hair.
- Get over here! Get me scissors! - Hey!
Stop it, Tae Hoon!
Hey, hey, hey. Stop it.
Seriously. Look how much you fight. Why would you go together?
Let's drink. Cheers.
Shut it, all of you!
Shut it, all of you.
Ju Kyung's passed out.
Are you sleeping, Ju Kyung?
Is he coming?
Why isn't he here yet? He should take care of her.
Here he is. Over here!
Hey. Who made Ju Kyung drink?
She drank on her own.
- Don't blame us. - Whatever.
- Let's drink. - Ju Kyung.
Hey, Ju Kyung. I'm here.
Okay? Wake up.
You're here.
- Seo Jun. - Yes?
You're dead!
Chen keeps bugging me because of you.
Hey. Stop it.
You'll knock over the drinks.
Stop it.
You're dead.
Pour some for her.
- Drink! - Stop it!
- I don't see you! - Hey. Hey.
Calm down.
Knock knock.
Knock knock. I want to go home.
- She's drunk. - She's wasted.
- You're drunk too. - Hey.
- You're kind of cute. - Ju Kyung.
Come on.
I'll take her home. You guys go without us.
- Okay. Bye. - Thanks. See you.
Come after.
- Let's go. - Where should we go?
Hey. Just get on my back.
No. I'm not drunk. I can walk.
Fine. Get over here. Come on.
I'm walking well.
- Wait. - I'm walking.
Get on my back. Get on.
Look. Small octopus. Hey, octopus.
Go to the ocean with me.
- Go to the ocean with me. - Hey.
I'll free you.
What are you doing?
- People eat that, you know. - I'm sorry, sir.
Taxi. Taxi!
Drive me home, please.
Where did she go?
- Let's go home. - What do you think you're doing?
- Let's go! - Miss...
I apologize for this. Ju Kyung, let's go.
Ju Kyung, come on.
- Let's go home. - Come here.
Hey, you are making me feel sick.
Have you snapped out of it?
If you have, you wouldn't have acted that way.
Grabbing a live small octopus out of the tank?
My stomach feels queasy from the way you carried me.
Then just throw it all up.
No, that'd be a waste.
I'm going to digest it all.
It'll all go down once I sit for a while.
You know how it is. I'm fine now.
Seo Jun.
Han Seo Jun.
What now?
Can you please meet with Chen just once?
I already declined.
Can't you make my life easier just this once?
Just agree to a meal with her.
Could you go on a date with someone you don't like?
I'm not asking you to be her boyfriend.
That's enough.
Just meet her this one time!
Stop telling me to meet other women...
because it annoys me to bits.
- Why's that? - Why?
Isn't it about time you knew how I felt?
My head...
Ju Young, pass me some water.
Cut back on the drinking, will you?
You're worse than Hee Kyung.
What?
Where did you just kick?
Did you sleep over last night?
How could I send him home...
when he carried you home hair wet from all the sweating?
Must you embarrass me in front of him?
Is that so?
I don't remember anything after I left the bar.
I completely blacked out.
You must be so proud.
I hear Seo Jun will make his debut soon.
Yes, we agreed on a concept...
and all we need to do is decide on a lead single.
Nice.
You can hand that over without washing it.
Once you make it big,
I'll sell it online as the clothes you wore.
Unbelievable.
Will we not get to see you often...
once you become a top celebrity?
Nonsense. I'll come by every day.
To see Ju Kyung?
No, to eat the food you make.
How is it better than what my mom makes?
I was known to be good at everything other than studying.
If you want, I can pack you some young radish kimchi.
Some?
I'd like a lot, please.
Sure. Eat up and I'll pack some for you.
It's for you to eat at your dorm.
Work hard and take care.
Ju Kyung.
- What? - About yesterday.
What about yesterday?
You really don't remember anything from when we left the bar?
No, I don't.
Did I behave indecently in any way?
You really don't remember?
Of course, I don't. Why would I lie to you?
Stop pretending that you don't remember.
This isn't me pretending. I don't remember a thing.
We kissed.
Let's go.
Hop on.
Let's go home.
Ms. Hong will be waiting for me.
Let's go.
Hey. We didn't kiss!
How can you know when you don't remember?
What?
So you do remember.
It's why you've been walking on eggshells around me all morning.
I've known you for years now.
What was I supposed to do?
And what if I do remember?
It'll only make things awkward between us.
You were just drunk and confused...
I wasn't confused...
and it wasn't a drunken mistake.
I never dreamed about telling you in this ridiculous way,
but you kept bringing Chen up and...
What does any of this matter though?
Just forget about it all.
Forget it happened and wait for me.
I'll properly tell you how I feel someday.
What on earth? Seo Jun likes me?
No way. I bet it's a joke.
Is it April Fool's Day?
It isn't.
Then why...
Since when?
Cho Rong, what do I do?
You waited two years to tell her how you feel,
but you finally did so out of anger and at her house...
while holding a container full of kimchi...
at eight in the morning...
looking like that?
I never confessed my feelings, all right?
I just told her I would someday.
It was like a teaser.
- A teaser? Are you kidding me? - Darn it.
Okay, fine. Just don't shed any tears.
I've been losing too much muscle to join you on the crying.
But maybe this is for the best.
If you hadn't gotten angry, Lee Soo Ho...
You would've thought...
you were betraying Soo Ho by telling her how you feel.
So it was for the best.
Now that the cat's out of the bag,
just keep pushing forward.
How does one confess his feelings?
Don't you watch TV dramas?
The guys you see in them...
rent an amusement park for the day,
have a helicopter fly above her,
or take her on a cruise ship...
to shoot fireworks into the sky.
I'm not rich, you know.
Where would I get the money?
Right. Of course.
Then, let your face do all the work.
Anything you do will look cool.
Check this out.
Fix your eyes with a longing gaze.
Once I drink this,
you'll be my girlfriend.
I won you over, didn't I?
Try it yourself.
Be my girlfriend.
My heart just skipped a beat.
My heart's pounding like crazy!
Seo Jun, do just that.
- Really? - She won't be able to refuse you.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Be my girlfriend.
Be my girlfriend, please.
Stop that, okay? My heart's skipping too many beats.
Don't do that either.
(Lim Jae Pil)
Hello, it's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Lim Jae Soon.
Hello, I'm Mr. Prince from Prince Comics.
I love you.
Seriously? You can't be that straightforward.
Let's change roles this time.
Hello,
- it's good to meet you. - Likewise.
What on earth...
- are you doing here though? - What do you mean?
A flower should be in a flower garden.
What are you up to?
I'm giving him pointers for his blind date tomorrow.
Really?
I hope it works out this time and you get to marry next year.
- I'll need a willing partner. - And she's out there.
She's out there somewhere, so get searching.
Take our Hee Kyung for example.
She's always been against marriage,
but she met a guy and will get married soon.
Just a second.
Jae Pil?
What's up with him?
He gets emotional whenever Hee Kyung's wedding is mentioned.
He must be upset to marry her off.
By the way, don't you get to know if Ju Young got into college today?
Yes, but I have no doubt he'll get into one.
All right...
(2022 Admission Results)
- Let's check at the same time. - No way.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Scissors.
- Nice! - Darn it.
You're up first.
Did I get in?
- No way. - Why? Did I not get in?
You got accepted!
Are you serious?
Ju Young, let's go out!
Nice! I'm so happy!
It's time to check yours now.
What? You didn't get in.
Forget what I said. I take it back.
What's with those two?
I thought they were best friends.
When did they start liking each other?
Isn't it about time you knew how I felt?
Let's eat dinner together tomorrow.
Don't bother trying to avoid me. Let's meet up and talk.
Forget it happened and wait for me.
I'll properly tell you how I feel someday.
I asked for the point brush.
I'm sorry.
- Just a second. - Move.
Get to your senses.
I don't need you right now, so go wait somewhere else.
I'm sorry.
You're in the way. Just go.
What's the matter with me?
Please sign this sheet and make a donation for kids in Africa.
Thank you.
Please sign this sheet.
Thank you. Please sign this sheet.
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Bye. Go home safely.
Ju Kyung.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
All the difficult times I had
Melt away like the snow
I still hope for
- Is there a girl? - He must be seeing someone.
- He's waiting for her text. - No, I'm not.
- Look at him. - See? It's a girl.
Okay, sure.
(- Let's eat dinner together. - Okay, sure.)
Let's meet tomorrow after you get off work.
(Let's meet tomorrow after you get off work.)
See you tomorrow.
I can't believe that beautiful fairy...
is going to be my wife.
My gosh, you're doing it again.
I don't need to wear this, right? And this is a little tight.
So get me a size bigger than this. I think I'm done trying on dresses.
Hee Kyung, you should try on more. You can try on three in total.
What do you think about trying on the bell line wedding dress?
I think that one will look nice on you.
What matters is that we're getting married.
The dress isn't important.
You're so easy-going.
Then should we let the groom pick out his tuxedo first?
Sure.
Hee Kyung.
What do you think?
You look great. Let's go with that one.
But wasn't the first one better?
The first one? This one looks similar.
- Tuxedos are all the same. - What are you talking about?
The first one was a black notch lapel tuxedo with a vest.
This one is a deep navy shawl lapel tuxedo...
with a cummerbund.
The one I tried on earlier had a straight collar.
But this one is round.
Depending on the collar, I could either look sharp or gentle.
It really has a big effect on my impression.
Do you know how important that is on the day of the wedding?
People will comment on whether or not you're marrying a handsome...
You're so handsome that the tuxedo doesn't even stand out.
You're not being serious.
Okay, fine. Try on the next one. This time, I'll be extra attentive.
Try on the next tuxedo.
- What do you think? - The tuxedo has found its owner.
You're glowing.
Really? This one's the same one I wore just a minute ago.
I didn't get changed.
What? My gosh.
You're lying.
We'll just call it a day.
Honey. Joon Woo. Joon Woo.
Honey.
Are you upset?
No, why would I be upset?
But it feels like I'm the only one getting married.
What are you talking about? You're marrying me.
It just feels like I'm the only one who's excited about the wedding.
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry, okay?
What are you sorry about?
Well...
I'm just sorry about everything.
Call me once you realize why you're sorry.
Joon Woo. Joon Woo!
My gosh, how am I going to make him feel better this time?
Mist.
Here.
I don't think I can walk. My feet hurt.
Just a second.
Here.
Go pick it up.
Chen, that's a bit too...
Seo Jun.
It's Seo Jun! Hey, Seo Jun!
Seo Jun, how did you know my album came in first place?
I can't believe you bought me flowers.
Here.
- Hey. - Yes?
- Do you have no hands? - Me?
Hands? I have hands.
Then go get it yourself.
- Hey. - Yes?
She can go home now that her schedule's done, right?
Yes, we're going to go home after we move everything.
- You can get off work, Ju Kyung. - No, I'll take everything upstairs.
- We'll be off now. - Okay.
- See you. - Let's go.
But...
I'm sorry. I'll be off now. I'll see you tomorrow.
Gosh, what's his problem?
- Why are you standing there? - What?
No, it's nothing.
But is it okay to come here dressed like this?
You look pretty.
You're holding it upside down.
- What do you think? - What?
It's delicious. It's nice here.
- Are you nervous? - No.
Why would I be nervous?
Well, I am.
After I told you how I felt yesterday,
I kept trying to come up with a fancy way to ask you out.
But I didn't want to make a fuss like people do in dramas or movies.
And I figured this place must be popular for a reason.
I'll just be straightforward with you.
I like you, Ju Kyung.
Seo Jun, I...
I've liked you for a long time.
But back then, I knew you liked someone else.
So I never got to ask you out, but I couldn't give up either.
It's been three years since I've felt this way for you.
But I can't keep it a secret anymore.
I keep finding myself wanting to tell you like I did yesterday.
So I can't hide it.
I just can't.
- Seo Jun... - I'm...
begging you to see me as a guy,
right now.
Sway a little.
Just once.
I'm not asking for an answer now.
Three dates.
Go on three dates with me.
As a guy and a girl.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Hey, what's wrong?
Do you feel sick?
- Here. - Thanks.
Gosh. I knew you'd get sick. You were eating so quickly.
Do you need medicine?
No. It was just a little indigestion.
Were you that uncomfortable?
No.
This is nice.
Be uncomfortable whenever you see me from now on.
I want you to be nervous around me...
and very aware of me as I am.
But don't get sick.
I'm...
begging you to see me as a guy, right now.
Sway a little.
Just once.
Why did you open this?
I really don't have the time to do this right now.
My dear brother-in-law. Thank you very much.
Get something to eat with this, my dear brother-in-law.
My dear brother-in-law. Why don't we put a heart...
at the end of the candle walkway?
Why don't we brothers-in-law do it together?
Where are you going?
To the convenience store.
Help us blow these up.
I'm dizzy. I can't do this any more.
- Are you crying? - It's really happening.
Hee Kyung's getting married.
There you go again.
Hee Kyung is the one who should cry, not you.
No.
I should tip her off.
It's a surprise. You can't tell her.
Honey.
Hey.
Joon Woo is over right now,
setting things up for a surprise proposal.
What? A proposal?
That's why he acted like he was upset earlier.
He's super excited about making it all moving,
so you have to cry.
Make yourself cry.
I can't force myself to cry.
Fine.
Why is he so cute?
How do I make myself cry?
Darn it. When was the last time I cried?
Here.
(Soju, Beef jerky)
It's the first snowfall already?
It's so annoying when it snows.
It's 5.7 dollars.
On the first day of snow, I'm going to go to Namsan...
and make a wish hoping that you'll remember me.
I love stuff like this.
The nightscape looks so pretty.
Soo Ho!
I'm sorry.
My girlfriend likes strawberries.
Hey.
Of course, I'm here.
It's cold, so dress warmly.
Maybe I should check my prescription.
I can't calm down.
(You're my world and every moment of my life.)
I didn't get to say any of this.
The flower meaning.
I forgot that too.
I forgot the flower meaning.
Drinking solo is the best.
It's snowing a lot.
What time is it?
May I see your ticket?
Did I drop it?
Just a second.
Found it.
(Heart Lock)
Ju Kyung?
Ju Kyung...
I came over here as soon as I landed...
and here you are.
Your face is freezing.
You must be cold.
Why are you back?
Because I missed you.
But we broke up.
So why did you miss me?
Still...
I still missed you.
I missed you so much.
I...
I haven't missed you at all.
Ju Kyung?
Ju Kyung!
Did you get home safely?
Are you here to practice at this late hour?
Yes, I didn't think I'll be able to sleep tonight.
Why's that? Are you nervous now that your debut is imminent?
Anyway, keep working hard.
By the way, Mr. Kang said that Soo Ho got in today.
- What? - Didn't you know?
His father gained consciousness last month.
The doctors called it a miracle. That's great news, right?
Yes, it is.
Anyway, don't exhaust yourself and head home soon. Bye.
Sure thing.
Would it have killed you to call?
The person you have reached is not available.
- What on earth? - Ju Kyung.
We should talk.
I don't want to see you right now.
Are you hurt? Ju Kyung.
No, just go away.
Are you all right?
Let me take you to a doctor.
I don't like seeing you sick.
Why are you still here?
I told you to leave me alone.
- How could I? - Just go.
I'm not going anywhere.
Then I'll leave instead.
How are you feeling?
I'm all right.
- Do you have her test results? - Yes.
Is there a serious issue with her?
- Not exactly. - If that's not the case,
why was she in so much pain?
What's the reason for it?
- Constipation. - Sorry?
Is that a serious illness?
Don't tell me I need surgery.
You have infrequent bowel movements.
Because of it, you felt temporary pain in your stomach.
The opaque parts on this image...
indicate built-up gas and stool.
For how long haven't you been able to go?
Don't be ridiculous. I poop just fine!
Drinking doesn't help with constipation.
Ju Kyung, wait. Ju Kyung!
You've got to be kidding me.
What do I do?
You're here with Mr. Lim, right?
Please follow me to the reception desk.
Sure.
(My beloved Hee Kyung, will you marry me?)
- I'll turn it on. - Here she comes.
The door opens
And you enter
At a first glance
I knew you were my sister-in-law-to-be
- Ju Kyung? - Was that Ju Kyung?
Yes, it was.
Just kill me already.
Why do I bother to live?
Talk about a humiliating reunion.
(Restricted Access)
My sweet Grapefruit, I'm touched!
I'm truly touched.
No, this is no good. We'll take it from the top.
Hee Kyung, go back outside. You'll make another entrance.
Darn it. But why?
- We have to do this again. - Are you kidding me?
- Come on. - Why must we do this?
It's all right. We'll just take it from the top.
Everything's fine, so take some deep breaths.
It sure isn't easy to get married, is it?
- Yes? - I dropped off your luggage.
I can't believe you ran off without heading home first.
Found it.
Ju Kyung?
Because it snowed.
I heard it was this year's first.
What? Use the car that's parked out front. It's your dad's.
Got it. Thank you for today.
(Girlfriend)
(Lee Soo Ho)
Did you go home safely?
(Missed call: Han Seo Jun)
- Seo Jun. - Hey.
How did you know?
I heard at the agency.
You're unbelievable.
- How could you not call? - I'm sorry.
I came in a rush, so I had a lot to take care of.
Your place hasn't changed at all.
- I only have water. - It's okay.
How's your dad?
Is he okay now?
Did he get discharged?
He's going to start getting rehabilitation therapy.
That's great news.
Hey, you should've visited me the moment you got here.
I can't believe you didn't call.
I kept calling you.
I didn't get a chance to.
I met Ju Kyung.
Really? You met her today?
Yes. By coincidence.
Are you crying?
(Woosam Snack)
It's just spicy. That's all.
You never had a problem eating spicy food.
Are you crying?
Did you check your college admission result?
Did you not get in? Is that why?
Then why are you crying?
Did something happen?
I miss him.
My gosh, that punk.
Then call him.
Judging by his personality, he broke up because he felt bad.
Do you want me to call him instead?
No. I'm going to get over him now.
I'm almost over him.
What's the matter with me today?
Maybe it's because it's snowing.
- Seo Jun. - Yes?
Did you eat? Should I order something?
Of course.
We haven't met in a while. Give me some updates.
Wait here.
My gosh, what a coincidence.
I can't believe I met you here.
What's going on?
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Don't follow me.
I'm not following you. I need to go this way as well.
That's another coincidence.
Did you eat breakfast?
Let me see your face.
Yesterday was the first day of snow. Why did you go to Namsan?
You thought of me, didn't you?
Ju Kyung, you were right. My wish actually came true.
Ju Kyung! Ju Kyung!
Your stomach might hurt again if you run! Ju Kyung!
Taxi. Taxi.
Ju Kyung! Ju Kyung!
He didn't even contact me for an entire year.
What does he want now?
Soo Ho.
How did you know about this place?
What a coincidence.
Is this where you work?
When do you finish work today?
Who told you? Was it Ju Young? Tae Hoon?
I swear it's just a coincidence.
Are you saying you came to a hair and makeup salon by coincidence?
Yes. I came to get my hair done.
Well, good luck getting your hair done.
Hey.
Is he an actor?
- I don't know. He's good-looking. - Excuse me.
Can I please get a drink?
I'm really thirsty.
What are you doing? Go get him a drink.
Okay.
He's handsome, so you should give him a lot.
Soo Ho doesn't like sweets.
Gosh, why do I still remember this stuff?
Like I care.
Does she not even eat?
You'll be done in 10 minutes.
Already?
Then can you straighten it back?
I changed my mind.
I'll be off now.
You did great, Ju Kyung.
- Bye. - Bye.
I guess he's gone.
Seo Jun?
Hey, you finished early.
- What are you doing here? - Do you have time for me today?
What?
You promised me three dates. Did you forget already?
Well... Yesterday...
You met Soo Ho, right?
You heard?
So what? That doesn't mean we can't hang out.
Today, I only want you to think about me.
It's the least you can do to someone who asked you out.
Okay, fine.
- What are we going to do? - Just follow my lead.
Whatever.
Where are we going?
Why do you want to ice-skate all of a sudden?
Guys take girls ice skating when they go on dates.
They help them when they're about to fall,
and that gives them a chance to become physically closer.
They can ice-skate and enjoy spending time together.
I'm not a good ice skater.
Neither am I.
- What? - What are we going to do?
Here. Let me do it for you.
Let's take a look.
You tied them well.
Hey. Hey, be careful.
I thought you weren't good.
Ju Kyung, let's make a bet.
The first person to get to that pillar is the winner.
- The winner gets to make a wish. - That's so typical of you.
Come on. Let's try. Instead, I'll go backward.
Ready?
1, 2, 3. Go.
- You're good. - I'm good, right?
- Careful. - Okay.
Ju Kyung.
Are you okay? Did you get badly hurt?
No, I'm okay.
Let's get you up.
1, 2, 3.
Is it bad?
No, it's just a small scratch.
- Give me that. I'll do it. - Let me see.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'll do it.
We shouldn't have made a bet.
Why do you like making bets so much?
Here. Throw it out for me.
I won, okay?
I want to look at earrings.
For Go Woon?
No, for myself.
Which one do you like more?
- I like this one. - This?
I'll take this.
She'll pay for it. Thanks.
What?
Hey, Seo Jun.
It changed a lot.
(Lim Ju Kyung's spot. Sit without permission, and get a hairy butt!)
After all this, you want to break up? Jerk.
I hope you get constipation.
Where are you?
I'll wait.
(Where are you? I'll wait.)
You bought me the earring, so I'll pay for this.
I should've ordered something expensive.
This is expensive.
It's good.
(Where are you? I'll wait.)
It's too rich. Do you want ice cream?
- What? - Excuse me.
- Yes? - Mint ice cream please.
- Okay. - Make it cold please.
Okay.
- Make it minty. - Okay.
(Comics)
You didn't have to walk me home.
It's because we're a guy and a girl today.
I wouldn't if we were friends.
You live too close to the station.
What do you mean? It's so far.
No, it isn't. It's super close.
We're here. Get home safely.
Ju Kyung.
Yes?
I'm...
using my wish.
(Prince Comics)
(Special thanks to Jung Joon Ho for his special appearance)
(Special thanks to Kim Young Dae for his special appearance)
(True Beauty)
Those memories don't hurt as much anymore.
I'm sorry.
Do you still like Ju Kyung?
No. We're going out.
Hey. It's Ju Kyung.
He's acting weird! He's all limp.
I'm going to start studying.
I want to learn properly from the basics.
Know something? It was my last day.
Don't go.
(He hunts humans.)
When will this hunt end?